<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/</link><description>Recent content on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amaretti</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/amaretti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/amaretti/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 1/4 cups almond flour or very finely ground almonds, sifted 1 cup granulated sugar pinch salt 2 large egg whites 1/4 teaspoon lemon juice 1/2 teaspoon almond extract confectioners’ sugar, as needed Directions Preheat oven to 300 degrees F. Stack two matching, heavyweight, cookie sheets together. Line with parchment paper or a silicone baking mat. In a large bowl, whisk together almond flour, sugar and salt until evenly incorporated.</description></item><item><title>Banana Bread - Gluten-free</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gluten-free-banana-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gluten-free-banana-bread/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 medium ripe bananas (3 bananas yield ~1 1/2 cups) 1/2 tsp pure vanilla extract 1 whole egg 3 Tbsp avocado or coconut oil, melted 1/4 cup organic cane sugar 1/4 cup packed organic brown sugar 2-3 Tbsp maple syrup (depending on ripeness of bananas // or sub honey) 3 1/2 tsp baking powder 3/4 tsp sea salt 1/2 tsp ground cinnamon 3/4 cup unsweetened almond milk (or other dairy-free milk) 1 1/4 cup almond meal 1 1/4 cup gluten-free flour blend 1 1/4 cup gluten-free oats Chocolate chips (optional) Directions Preheat oven to 350 degrees F and line a 9×5-inch loaf pan with parchment paper.</description></item><item><title>Boulevardier</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/boulevardier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/boulevardier/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 - 1.25 part Rye Whiskey (Bourbon for sweeter) 1 part Campari 1 part Sweet Vermouth Directions Combine over ice Stir Serve in chilled glass Garnish with orange peel</description></item><item><title>Brandacujun</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</guid><description>Description Dried cod (stockfish) with potatoes.
Ingredients Salted, dried cod 1 kg potatoes (about 7) 2 garlic cloves, crushed 3 tbsp minced parsley 1 tbsp olive oil Directions Soak the fish in water for 24 hours, changing the water every few hours; this removes some of the salt and softens the dry fish Cut into pieces</description></item><item><title>Brazilian Stew</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brazilian-stew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brazilian-stew/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 tablespoon oil 1 medium onion, chopped 2 cloves garlic, minced 2 sweet potatoes, peeled, diced 1 large red bell pepper, diced 1 cans diced tomatoes 1 hot green chili pepper, diced 2 cups vegetable stock plus 1 1/2 cups of water 2 cans black beans Serve and top with: 1 mango, peeled and diced 1/4 cup chopped fresh cilantro 1 lime (or whatever you want) Directions Cook onion, garlic, sweet potato and bell pepper until soft.</description></item><item><title>Cannarìculi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</guid><description>Description pasta arrotolata della lunghezza di un pollice cotta in olio bollente e ricoperta di miele
Ingredients 1 cup flour 1 egg 1/2 cup white wine 1/2 cup oil (light vegetable oil, like sunflower) 1/2 t. baking powder 2 t. sugar Directions Mix ingredients Make a long and round rope Cut 1&amp;quot; pieces and fry in oil Roll in honey when still hot</description></item><item><title>Cantuccini</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</guid><description>Description Biscotti
Ingredients 2 cups+1 tablespoon) all-purpose flour sifted 3/4 cup + 1 tablespoon) granulated sugar 1 tablespoon honey 1 teaspoon baking powder 1 teaspoon grated orange zest or lemon zest 1 teaspoon amaretto or 1/2 teaspoon almond extract (optional) 2 eggs ½ cup raw unpeeled almonds Directions Preheat the oven to 180 degrees C (356 degrees F). In a large bowl, combine the dry ingredients. Add the eggs, honey, orange zest, amaretto and mix all the ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Caponata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/caponata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/caponata/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/4 c. Olive oil 1 large carrot chopped (1/2”) 1 large onion chopped 2-3 stalks celery chopped 1 firm eggplant, peeled and chopped 1 can petite diced tomatoes 1 can water or vegetable stock 2 T. Capers 2 T. red wine vinegar 4 oz black and/ or green sliced olives Parsley, chopped fine Directions Sauté carrot, onion, and celery until soft Add eggplant and stir until all coated with oil mix Add tomatoes, water and cook over medium heat until very soft, about 20 min.</description></item><item><title>Castagnaccio</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g di farina di castagne 1 litro di acqua 50 g di zucchero di canna biologico (facoltativo) 150 g di uvetta 20 g circa di pinoli italiani ½ cucchiaio di semini di finocchietto 5 cucchiai di olio extravergine di oliva ligure sale fino marino Directions Sciacquate l&amp;rsquo;uva passa, e lasciatela in ammollo circa 30 minuti in acqua tiepida. In una terrina molto capiente versate tutta la farina di castagne setacciandola, in modo da non creare grumi.</description></item><item><title>Cenci</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cenci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cenci/</guid><description>Description Mardi Gras dessert
Ingredients 1 3/4 cups (225 g) flour 2 tablespoons unsalted butter 1/3 cup confectioners sugar 2 eggs 1 tablespoon brandy A pinch of salt More confectioner’s sugar for dusting Oil for deep frying Directions Make a fairly stiff dough with these ingredients, kneading it thoroughly, and adding more flour if it comes out too soft. Flour it and let it rest, covered tightly with plastic wrap, for about an hour.</description></item><item><title>Chestnut Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chestnut-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chestnut-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 lb. roasted chestnuts (2 cups) 1/2 c. pine nuts, toasted 1 c. sugar 4 eggs separated 10 T. butter, room temperature 1 t. vanilla 4 ounces semisweet chocolate Directions Preheat oven to 350 degrees. Butter an 8-inch springform pan and line the bottom with parchment or waxed paper. Butter the paper and flour the pan. In a large mixing bowl, beat the egg yolks and sugar until the mixture is pale and thick enough to leave a ribbon, 2 to 3 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Piccata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chicken-piccata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chicken-piccata/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 large boneless and skinless chicken breasts, halved horizontally to make 4 2 tablespoons flour (all purpose or plain) 2 tablespoons finely grated fresh Parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon salt Cracked pepper For The Sauce:
Light spray of cooking oil 1 tablespoon olive oil 2 teaspoons butter (or oil) 2 tablespoons minced garlic 1¼ cup chicken broth (stock) ½ cup milk (full fat or 2% &amp;ndash; or use reduced fat cream or heavy cream) ⅓ cup finely grated fresh Parmesan cheese 2 tablespoons capers (plus 2 tablespoons extra to garnish) 1 teaspoon cornstarch (cornflour) mixed with 1 tablespoon of water 2-3 tablespoons lemon juice &amp;ndash; juice of 1 lemon (adjust to your tastes) 2 tablespoons fresh parsley Directions Lightly spray pan/skillet with a light coating of cooking oil spray and heat over medium-hight heat.</description></item><item><title>Chili - Sweet Potato and Black Bean</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chili-sweet-potato-and-black-bean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chili-sweet-potato-and-black-bean/</guid><description>Ingredients Olive oil Medium onion, diced 2 garlic cloves, minced 1 large sweet potato, peeled and diced Large can (28 oz) diced tomatoes 2 cans black beans 2 cups water 2 T mild chili powder (or 1 if too spicy) 2 tsp paprika 2 tsp cumin 1 tsp salt Directions Saute onion in oil until transparent, 3-4 minutes Add garlic and sweet potato, 2 minutes Add spices, stir and let coat sweet potatoes Add tomatoes, beans, water Bring to a boil Simmer uncovered, 20-25 minutes</description></item><item><title>Coffee Kranz</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough
1/2 lb. margarine 3 egg yolks 2 Tbsp sugar 1 t salt 1 package dry yeast 4 cups sifted flour 1 cup milk Cheese Filling (makes 3 cups)
2 large (8 oz) cream cheese 1 cup sugar 1 egg 1 t vanilla Directions For dough:
Combine all ingredients in order into one bowl Mix as for pie crust using a pastry cutter Add milk and mix (with hands) Cover and refrigerate over night Cheese filling:</description></item><item><title>Cranberry Relish</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-relish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-relish/</guid><description>Ingredients 1lb. Cranberries 1 orange, diced 1/3c. Sugar Directions Place in processor and process until well chopped</description></item><item><title>Cranberry Sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-sauce/</guid><description>Ingredients 1lb. Cranberries 1 orange, diced 1 piece of candied ginger 1 stick of cinnamon 1/3 c. Sugar 1c. Water Directions Place all in a saucepan and cover with water. Bring to boil and cook until cranberries pop. Cool and serve.</description></item><item><title>Creole Shrimp Skewers</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/creole-shrimp-skewers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/creole-shrimp-skewers/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 tablespoons Creole Seasoning 6 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted 1 pound medium shrimp (30/40) peeled and deveined Directions
Preheat the oven to 425 degrees F. Combine the Creole Seasoning and melted butter in a medium bowl. Whisk to combine. Place 3 tablespoons of this mixture in a shallow dish and reserve the remaining mixture for later. Skewer the shrimp on small 6 inch skewers, using 2-3 shrimp per skewer.</description></item><item><title>Crispi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 cups of flour 1 package of yeast 1T. salt 1-2 cups water Oil for frying Directions Mix as you would for making a pizza. This dough will be a lot stickier Let rise until doubled Dip your hands into a bowl of oil, shape a bit of dough into a round doughnut or ring and drop into a pan full of very hot oil until golden brown.</description></item><item><title>David's No Knead Baguette</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/baguette-no-knead/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/baguette-no-knead/</guid><description>Description David&amp;rsquo;s No Knead Baguette
Ingredients 5 cups bread flour 1 c. all-purpose flour 1/2 tsp yeast 2 tsp salt 3 1/4 c. water Directions 18 hour 1st rise 2 hour 2nd rise optional 12 hour retard Shape 4 loaves Bake 2 at a time Mist with water before putting in oven 475 until done</description></item><item><title>Easy Lasagne</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/easy-lasagne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/easy-lasagne/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 pkg chopped frozen spinach-thawed and squeezed of water 1 lb. ricotta 1/2 c. grated parmesan Salt, pepper 2 cups tomato sauce 1/2 lb. shredded mozzarella 1/2 pkg oven ready lasagne Directions Mix spinach, ricotta, grated cheese, salt, pepper and set aside Place a layer of sauce in an 8x8 baking dish Top with noodles, spinach mix, mozzarella and sauce Repeat until all used Cover with foil and bake for 30 min in 400 degree oven Remove foil and bake 10 more minutes</description></item><item><title>Emeril's Essence Creole Seasoning</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/emeril-s-essense/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/emeril-s-essense/</guid><description>Description Creole Seasoning (also referred to as Bayou Blast)
Ingredients 2 1/2 tablespoons paprika 2 tablespoons salt 2 tablespoons garlic powder 1 tablespoon black pepper 1 tablespoon onion powder 1 tablespoon cayenne pepper 1 tablespoon dried oregano 1 tablespoon dried thyme</description></item><item><title>Farinata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 c. Garbanzo flour 1 c. Water 1 t. Salt 1 t. Pepper 1 t. Rosemary or other herb Oil Directions Whisk flour, water, salt, pepper, herbs and 1 T. Oil Refrigerate for 1-2 hrs Preheat a cast iron pan in 450 oven Pour 2+T. Oil in pan, add the batter and bake for 5-10min</description></item><item><title>Fettuccine with Shrimp</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/fettuccine-with-shrimp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/fettuccine-with-shrimp/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. Olive oil 1 medium onion sliced thinly Dash of peperoncino 1 can petite diced tomatoes 1/3 c. White wine Salt, pepper, rosemary 1 lb. shrimp (8-10 per person, depending on size) 1/2 lb fettuccine, cooked al dente Basil Directions Sauté onion in oil until transparent Add peperoncino, tomatoes and wine Cook down Add salt, pepper, rosemary and shrimp Cook until shrimp is pink Add this to cooked pasta and serve Top with basil or parsley</description></item><item><title>Flourless Chocolate Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/flourless-chocolate-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/flourless-chocolate-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients ½ cup water ¼ tsp sea salt ¾ cup granulated sugar 18 oz (2 ¼ cups) bittersweet chocolate chips (or chopped chocolate)* 1 cup salted butter, room temperature or Earth’s Balance 6 eggs, room temperature 1 tsp pure vanilla extract Directions Preheat oven to 300 degrees F. Grease one 9” round cake pan (or glass pie plate) and set aside. (Note: I always cut a piece of parchment paper into a circle with “handles” and place it on the bottom of the pan.</description></item><item><title>Focaccia</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/foccacia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/foccacia/</guid><description>Description Almost no-knead focaccia, developed by David based on Grandma Giordano&amp;rsquo;s recipe (that wasn&amp;rsquo;t written down)
Ingredients 7 1/2 cups flour, 1/2 bread, 1/2 all purpose 1 tsp yeast 3 cups water 1 T salt Biga (old dough), about 1/2 cup. Skip if you don&amp;rsquo;t have Oil/salt for top Directions Preheat to 450 Mix flour, yeast, biga, water Add salt Knead until dough comes together, should be tacky Coat in oil and let rise overnight (8-24 hours) Stretch dough in jelly roll pan (or round) Let rise 1-2 hours Using hands, push dimples into dough, almost through to the pan Spray with water Coat in oil and sprinkle salt Put in oven (on tiles preferably) Add ice to a metal pan on floor of oven (for steam) Drop temp to 400 Bake 20-25 minutes</description></item><item><title>French Onion Soup</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/french-onion-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/french-onion-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 T olive oil 3 or more onions, sliced 1 bouillon cube 4 cups water 1 T flour (optional) Directions Cook onions in oil until brown Add flour, bouillon cube, and water Bring to boil, then simmer for 1 hour Place 1 slice Italian bread topped with Swiss cheese in a bowl Top with soup</description></item><item><title>Frizzuli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/frizzuli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/frizzuli/</guid><description>Ingredients flour-one handful per person 2 eggs Water Directions None provided</description></item><item><title>Gnocchi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 medium potatoes, cooked and riced 1 t. Salt, 1 t. Pepper 1 egg 1 c. Flour Directions Cook the potatoes in their skin. Cool and rice Add the rest of ingredients to the potatoes Form a long rope of about a foot Cut rope every one inch Run each over a grater to form indentation; or use a fork Cook in plenty of salted water They are done when they come to the top Serve with any sauce</description></item><item><title>Gnocchi Verdi: Spinach and Ricotta Gnocchi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gnocchi-verdi-spinach-and-ricotta-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gnocchi-verdi-spinach-and-ricotta-gnocchi/</guid><description>Description Spinach and ricotta gnocchi with butter and sage sauce
Ingredients 1 pkg frozen, chopped spinach, thawed, cooked (3 minutes in microwave) and water squeezed out 1 lb. ricotta cheese 1 egg 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese 3/4 cup flour 1 tsp salt 1/2 tsp nutmeg 4 T unsalted butter 1T fresh sage (dried can be substituted) Directions Mix together spinach, ricotta, egg, nutmeg and salt Fold in 4 Tablespoons Parmesan and 1/2 c flour Spread 1/4 c flour on a plate Drop 1/2 t.</description></item><item><title>Grandma Bellino's Meatballs</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-meatballs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-meatballs/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/2 lb. ground beef 1/2 lb. ground pork 1 T. Italian seasonings 1 egg 1/2 c. Grated cheese 1/2 c. Breadcrumbs Salt, pepper, diced garlic, chopped parsley Directions Mix all ingredients together Form medium size balls Fry or bake Add to tomato sauce and cook together Serve over pasta</description></item><item><title>Grandma Bellino's Pizza</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-pizza/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-pizza/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 C. Flour 1 pkg yeast (proof in 1/2 C. Warm water and 1/2 t. Sugar) 1 t. Salt 1 c. Warm water 1 red pepper, sliced thinly 1 large onion, sliced thinly 2 cloves garlic, sliced thinly Tomato sauce 1 T. Italian seasonings 1/2 lb. shredded mozzarella salt, pepper Peperoncino (sprinkled on top after baking) Directions In a mixing bowl place the flour, salt and yeast mixture.</description></item><item><title>Green Bean Casserole</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/green-bean-casserole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/green-bean-casserole/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 (10.75 ounce) cans Campbell&amp;rsquo;s® Condensed Cream of Mushroom Soup 1 cup milk 2 teaspoons soy sauce 1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper 8 cups cooked cut green beans 2 2/3 cups French&amp;rsquo;s® French Fried Onions Directions Stir soup, milk, soy sauce, pepper, beans and 1 1/3 cups onions in 3-qt. casserole. Bake at 350 degrees F. for 25 min. or until hot. Stir. Top with remaining onions.</description></item><item><title>Hummus</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/hummus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/hummus/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 can chick peas 2 cloves garlic lemon juice Oil or tahini Cumin Paprika Salt Directions Mix in food processor Add water to thin if necessary Variations
Add roasted red peppers Use white beans</description></item><item><title>Insalata Russa</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</guid><description>Description Grandma Giordano made this for special occasions, especially Easter.
Ingredients 1 lb frozen peas, cooked according to package 1 lb frozen cubed carrots, cooked according to package 2 large potatoes boiled and cubed Mayonnaise Directions Mix all together. Shape into oval and decorate with Olives, gherkins, capers, anchovies</description></item><item><title>Italian Pear Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/italian-pear-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/italian-pear-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 9 Tbsp unsalted butter at room temperature 9 Tbsp white sugar 2 large eggs 7 Tbsp all-purpose flour 3.5 oz ground almonds 1/2 tsp baking powder 3 medium pears ripe, peeled, cored and halved 1.7 oz flaked almonds Icing sugar for garnish Directions
Pre-heat oven to 375° F. Grease an 8-inch springform pan and line the bottom with a round of parchment paper. Set aside. Prepare pears, by peeling, coring and cutting in half.</description></item><item><title>Jambalaya</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jambalaya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jambalaya/</guid><description>Ingredients 12 medium shrimp, peeled, deveined and chopped 4 ounces chicken, diced 1 tablespoon Creole seasoning, recipe follows 2 tablespoons olive oil 1/4 cup chopped onion 1/4 cup chopped green bell pepper 1/4 cup chopped celery 2 tablespoons chopped garlic 1/2 cup chopped tomatoes 3 bay leaves 1 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1 teaspoon hot sauce 3/4 cup rice 3 cups chicken stock 5 ounces Andouille sausage, sliced Salt and pepper Directions In a bowl combine shrimp, chicken and Creole seasoning, and work in seasoning well.</description></item><item><title>Jan Hagel</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: Mom always made these for Christmas and everybody thought that they were Italian cookies, but I had found this recipe in a magazine when I was in high school and we always made them together. It’s a Swedish (or maybe Dutch) cookie.​​
Ingredients 1 1/2 c. flour ​3/4 c. sugar ​½ t. cinnamon ​½ c. butter ​1 egg ​1 egg white ​½ c. Slivered almonds Directions ​In large bowl combine flour, ½ c.</description></item><item><title>King Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/king-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/king-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 roll frozen bread dough, thawed 8 ounces cream cheese, softened 1 cup powdered sugar 1 teaspoon lemon extract For the Icing: 1-1/2 cups confectioner’s sugar 3 tablespoons milk (more if needed but stir this amount first, you’ll be surprised how far this goes!) 1 tsp clear butter or vanilla flavoring Directions On floured surface, roll out your dough to a rectangle of about 10 x 18 inches.</description></item><item><title>La Sardenaira</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 cups flour 2 cups of warm water 1 pk of yeast 3 T. oil 1 T. salt 1 t. sugar Directions Mix the above together and let rise. Place dough in a pan and top with the following 1 can peeled tomatoes Oregano Garlic in their peel anchovies (optional) Olives - (taggiasche); substitute black cured Capers (optional) Olive oil Bake in a hot oven (475) until done (15 min) Notes Original recipe in Italian:</description></item><item><title>Lemon Chicken</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/lemon-chicken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/lemon-chicken/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 chicken breasts sliced crosswise and pounded until thin 4 T. flour seasoned with salt and pepper 2 T. Oil 1/4 c. lemon juice 1/2 c. stock/wine Directions Dredge chicken in flour and fry in oil until golden Add lemon juice and stock and cook over low heat until done Serve with pan drippings and a slice of lemon</description></item><item><title>Negroni (Negroski)</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/negroni-negroski/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/negroni-negroski/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 part Gin (or Vodka) 1 part Campari 1 part Sweet Vermouth Directions Combine over ice Stir Serve in chilled glass Garnish with orange peel</description></item><item><title>Nonna Pancakes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-pancakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-pancakes/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 egg 1 banana cinnamon Directions Mash banana and mix with egg Add cinnamon to taste Pan fry as normal pancakes</description></item><item><title>Nonna's Butter Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-butter-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-butter-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 2c. Flour 1c. Butter 2c. Sugar (1 cup) 1 beaten egg Dash of salt Sliced almonds Directions Keep half the beaten egg for top Knead all ingredients into smooth paste Butter a pie pan or spring form pan Press dough into it Brush with rest of beaten egg Press almonds on top Bake 30min. at 350 Questions: why is 2 c sugar followed by (1 cup)?</description></item><item><title>Nonna's Chocolate Pudding</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-chocolate-pudding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-chocolate-pudding/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 Ripe avocado 2 t Cocoa powder 1 t honey or agave nectar 1/2 t water Directions Blend until smooth</description></item><item><title>One Pot Enchilada</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/one-pot-enchilada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/one-pot-enchilada/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup quinoa 1 can black beans 1 sweet potato, 1/2&amp;quot; pieces 2 cups corn (can be frozen) 1 can diced tomatoes 1 can/packet enchilada sauce (10 oz) 1/2 cup water (we usually need more, probably closer to a cup) 2 cups kale or spinach (optional) 1/2 cup shredded cheese (optional) Seasoning: 1 tsp chili powder 1 tsp cumin 1/2 tsp paprika 1/4 tsp onion powder 1/4 tsp garlic powder salt to taste Directions Put all in a pan/pot Bring to boil Reduce to simmer Cover Cook 20 min or until quinoa is done, stirring occasionally.</description></item><item><title>Paolo's sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/dadssauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/dadssauce/</guid><description>Notes My mom always added butter at the end to give it a more velvety taste. I haven’t done it but it’s an option
Ingredients 1 large onion chopped and sautéed until translucent Olive oil (quello buono) 1 Large can of crushed tomatoes 1 Pomì of strained tomatoes Salt, pepper to taste Rosemary (fresh if possible) Directions Cover the bottom of the pan with oil on medium heat When oil is beginning to sizzle add the onion and rosemary.</description></item><item><title>Pasta alla Puttanesca</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-alla-puttanesca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-alla-puttanesca/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. oil 4 cloves garlic, minced 1/4 c. chopped olives 1/4 c. capers 1 t. red pepper flakes 1 can tuna 1 can diced tomatoes Juice of 1/2 lemon zest of lemon Parsley 1/2 lb pasta Directions no directions included Variations David and Stephanie make this with spaghetti squash; no tuna or lemon. We use kalamata olives.</description></item><item><title>Pasta con Panna, Prosciutto, e Piselli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-con-panna-prosciutto-e-piselli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-con-panna-prosciutto-e-piselli/</guid><description>Description Pasta with cream, ham/prosciutto, and peas
Ingredients 1 lb spaghetti 1 c. diced ham 1 pk. frozen peas 1 stick butter 1 quart half and half 1 c cheese salt pepper Directions Melt butter, cook ham and peas in butter Add cream Cook spaghetti Add spaghetti to cream mixture, cook while stirring Toss with 1 c. cheese, salt, pepper to taste</description></item><item><title>Pasta with Ceci</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-with-ceci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-with-ceci/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. Olive oil 2 cloves garlic, chopped Dash of peperoncino 1 can petite diced tomatoes or 1 cup tomato sauce 1 can garbanzo beans Salt, pepper, oregano 1/2 lb. short pasta like farfalle 1/2 c. Grated Parmesan cheese Directions Sauté garlic in olive oil until golden Add. tomatoes, peperoncino, salt, pepper and oregano and cook Add beans and cook until soft Add some water as needed Add cooked pasta to the skillet and toss with cheese</description></item><item><title>Pat O'Brien's Hurricane</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pat-o-brien-s-hurricane/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pat-o-brien-s-hurricane/</guid><description>Ingredients 1oz vodka 1/4oz grenadine 1oz gin 1oz light rum 1/2oz 151 rum 1oz amaretto 1oz triple sec Grapefruit juice Pineapple juice</description></item><item><title>Peach Cobbler</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/peach-cobbler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/peach-cobbler/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/4-1/2 c. sugar 1 c. Bisquick 1 egg 1/4 c. milk or water 1 can peaches Topping:
2 T. Bisquick 1 T. butter 2 T. brown sugar Directions Mix dough Add peach slices Add topping Bake 350, 20-30 minutes Notes This cobbler is Rosa&amp;rsquo;s recipe, using bisquick. It can be made with other fruit, like blueberries.</description></item><item><title>Pesto</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</guid><description>Description Pesto can be made and frozen. If frozen do not add cheese or nuts; you can add those later, if you want.
Ingredients Basil Olive oil Garlic, multiple cloves Salt Parmesan cheese (optional) Pine nuts (optional) Directions Mix together in food processor Use right away or store in refrigerator (add oil to cover); or freeze When ready to use, warm up, add to pasta with a square of butter.</description></item><item><title>Pickled Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients water vinegar button mushrooms Directions Boil 1/2 water and 1/2 vinegar Add button mushrooms for 5 minutes Drain Cool mushrooms with lemons and peppercorns Place in jars Fill with vinegar Questions:
sliced lemons? How many? Do you put the lemons in the jars? I don&amp;rsquo;t remember lemons. White vinegar? Fill with vinegar - new vinegar, the vinegar/water mix? How many peppercorns? Black peppercorns? Amounts?</description></item><item><title>Pitte ’N Chiuse</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 C. Flour 3 T. Oil 1 t. Salt 1 C. Water In the meantime, chop 2 bunches Swiss Chards Add 1/2 to 1 C. Raisins Pinch of peperoncino  Salt and pepper Directions Mix together and let it rest covered Let it rest a good hr, at which time squeeze out any moisture Pinch off some dough and form a thin circle about 7-10 inches Place a dollop of Swiss chard, wet all around and fold like a turnover  Bake for 30 min in 400 degree oven</description></item><item><title>Pupuwignognuwu - Easter Babies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pupuwignognuwu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pupuwignognuwu/</guid><description>Description Easter babies
Ingredients 1c. Milk 1/2 stick of butter 1/2 c. Sugar 1 pkg of yeast 4 eggs + 3 more for inside 4 c. Flour Egg wash (mix one egg with 1 T. water) Icing-optional (1 c. Confectioners sugar mixed with warm milk) Original:
1 kg.di farina, 1 cucchiaio raso di sale, 4 uova, 1 bicchiere di olio,1 bicchiere di vino bianco, 12 gr. di lievito di birra.</description></item><item><title>Raschiatelli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/raschiatelli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/raschiatelli/</guid><description>Ingredients Flour one handful per person Water Directions None provided</description></item><item><title>Ratatouille</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ratatouille/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ratatouille/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 can (28 ounces) whole peeled tomatoes 6 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil 1 large eggplant (1 pound), cut into 1-inch Coarse salt and ground pepper 2 large yellow onions (1 pound total), diced 1 head garlic, cloves smashed and peeled 2 bell peppers (any color), seeded and diced 2 large zucchini (1 pound total), diced large 1 bay leaf 1 tablespoon fresh marjoram or oregano 2 to 3 tablespoons red-wine vinegar Directions</description></item><item><title>Ravioli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 cups all-purpose flour, plus more for dusting 1 teaspoon salt 3 large eggs, plus 1 for egg wash 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil Cornmeal, for dusting FILLING
1lb chopped, frozen spinach, microwaved and squeezed almost dry 1lb ricotta 1 egg 1/2 c. grated cheese Salt, pepper Dash of nutmeg Directions Combine the flour and salt on a flat work surface; shape into a mound and make a well in the center.</description></item><item><title>Risotto ai Funghi Porcini</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/risotto-ai-funghi-porcini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/risotto-ai-funghi-porcini/</guid><description>Ingredients T. oil Small onion, finely chopped 1 cup arborio rice 1/4 cup (splash) white wine (optional) 1 cup vegetable stock or 1 bouillon cube in cup of hot water Handful dried mushrooms, soaked in 1 cup hot water Parmesan Salt/pepper to taste Directions Saute onion until translucent (mom&amp;rsquo;s recipe always said opaque - it&amp;rsquo;s now an inside joke) Add rice; stir, coating rice with oil; cook a little Add wine Add liquid, little bit at a time (like 1/2 cup), stirring constantly.</description></item><item><title>Rosette</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/rosette/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/rosette/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 1/2 c. flour 2 eggs 2 T sugar Directions Mix, roll flat Cut in ribbon, form in rosettes Fry in oil Top with honey and ground nuts QUESTIONS: how much honey? what type of nuts? What&amp;rsquo;s a rosette - a spiral? Do we have a pic?</description></item><item><title>Sausage and Peppers</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sausage-and-peppers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sausage-and-peppers/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. Olive oil 1 red pepper, sliced 1 yellow pepper, sliced 1 large onion, sliced Salt, pepper 5-6 sausage links (I prefer hot Italian) Directions Sauté vegetable in oil with salt and pepper Remove vegetables from pan and add sausages Brown sausages on all sides Add the vegetables, some water, and cook over medium heat until sausages are done</description></item><item><title>Scalloped Potatoes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/scalloped-potatoes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/scalloped-potatoes/</guid><description>Directions In a baking pan, place one layer 4c. Potatoes sliced thinly Meanwhile in a saucepan mix 3T. Butter 3T. Flour 11/2 c. Milk 1t. Salt Top the first layer with the sauce, top with more potatoes, sauce and 1c. Sharp cheddar Top with 1/2c. Grated cheese Paprika Bake 350 for 1 hour</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description></item><item><title>Site Index</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/siteindex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/siteindex/</guid><description>&amp;ndash;
SiteIndex This page exists to respond to a site index. It uses layouts/siteindex/single</description></item><item><title>Spinach Ricotta Pie</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 frozen pie crusts - bake as directed 2 10 oz frozen chopped spinach, thawed and all water squeezed out 1 lb ricotta 1 can evaporated milk 3 eggs 1 T. instant dry onion 1/2 t salt 1/4 t pepper 1/4 t ground nutmeg 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Preheat oven, 350 degrees Mix ricotta with next 7 ingredients Add spinach Place in crusts and cook for 50 minutes, 350 degrees</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 1/2 lb. baby Bella mushrooms 2 tbsp. butter 2 cloves garlic, minced 1/4 c. breadcrumbs Kosher salt Freshly ground black pepper 1/4 c. freshly grated Parmesan, plus more for topping 4 oz. cream cheese, softened 2 tbsp. freshly chopped parsley, plus more for garnish 1 tbsp. freshly chopped thyme Directions Clean the mushrooms and remove the stems Chop the stems and sauté in butter and garlic Add to the rest of ingredients and stuff the mushrooms with this mix Place the mushrooms in a baking dish and bake in 350 oven for 20-30 min Shortcut: Add a cup of spinach artichoke Parmesan spread to the sautéed stems.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 3 medium size potatoes  4 tablespoon of extra-virgin olive oil  1 medium size onions, minced 1lb medium size white onions 2 eggs, lightly beaten 3 tablespoons freshly grated parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon of marjoram leaves, minced 1 tablespoon of fresh Italian (flat) parsley, minced fine sea salt to taste pepper to taste 1 cup fine unflavoured bread crumbs Directions Wash the potatoes, put them with their peel into a pot filled with cold water and boil for about 35 minutes or until tender.</description></item><item><title>Sugo di Carne</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sugo-di-carne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sugo-di-carne/</guid><description>Ingredients 4T. Olive oil 2 cloves of garlic 1lb. Beef chuck short ribs- boneless 1lb. Pork shoulder country style ribs-boneless 1 28oz. Tomato purée 2T. Tomato paste 1T. Salt 1t. Pepper 2 sprigs rosemary Directions Brown garlic in the oil and remove when golden Add the meat and sauté until nicely browned Add all other ingredients and bring to a boil Turn to simmer and cook for at least 2 hrs.</description></item><item><title>Taco Seasoning - nightshade free</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taco-seasoning-nightshade-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taco-seasoning-nightshade-free/</guid><description>Description Found this recipe when eliminating inflammatory foods. It&amp;rsquo;s really good on shrimp for tacos.
Ingredients 2 TB garlic powder 2 TB onion powder 2 TB ground turmeric 1 tsp ground ginger 1 tsp ground cinnamon 1 tsp dried oregano 1 tsp sea salt Directions Combine all seasonings in a glass container with a lid Shake well until combined Notes Originally from Clean Eating Veggie Girl: https://cleaneatingveggiegirl.</description></item><item><title>Taralli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taralli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taralli/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 1 cup flour 120 grams 2 tablespoons olive oil 30 grams 4 tablespoons white wine 60 grams 1/2 teaspoon salt 2 1/2 grams 1/2 tablespoon fennel seeds if desired I&amp;rsquo;m sure sesame seeds would work too Directions In a large bowl whisk flour, salt and fennel seeds together, add olive oil and wine combine with a wooden spoon, place on a flat surface and knead for approximately 10 minutes until dough is smooth and elastic.</description></item><item><title>Tiramisu</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs, separated 1/2 cup sugar 1/2 lb. light or fat-free ricotta 1/3 cup heavy cream 1 pkg lady fingers 2 T rum 1/3 cup espresso 1 bar chocolate, 3 oz Directions Combine egg yolks and sugar. Beat until light Mix in 1 cup ricotta, combined with cream Blend in rum Beat egg whites until stiff. Fold into cheese mixture. Refrigerate Shred chocolate over top</description></item><item><title>Torroncino</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: This recipe comes from Adriana Scalora a former student of mine at LTHS (1979-2003). I’ve made them for Christmas ever since she gave me the recipe in the late 80s.
Ingredients 1/4 c. honey 1 ½ c. sugar 1 lb. Skinless slivered almonds, toasted 2 T. sesame seeds, toasted 1 t. diced orange peel Directions Bring honey to a boil Add sugar and stir until dissolved Add orange peel and almonds and cook stirring for 2-3 min.</description></item><item><title>Torta di Patate</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</guid><description>Description Torta di Patate, without sfoglia: Potato pie, recipe without the crust. Use the crust from Torta verde
Ingredients 4 medium potatoes boiled in their skin, cooled and riced 1 egg Salt, pepper, nutmeg 1/2 c. Grated Parmesan 1/2 c. Bread crumbs 1/2 c. Milk Directions Mix all together Place 1/2 mixture in a greased pie pan Top with sliced ham and/or mozzarella, if using Top with remaining potato mixture Top with a film of olive oil Bake for 45 min.</description></item><item><title>Torta Verde</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough:
3 cups flour 1 cup warm water 3/4 cup oil 1 T salt Inside:
2 big bunches Swiss chard chopped and steamed. Can substitute spinach 4 small-med zucchini, shredded 1/2 bag frozen or 2 cans artichokes chopped fine 3 eggs 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese (or Romano) Handful of rice Directions Dough:
Mix until smooth dough forms Flour surface to roll out dough; divide dough Roll out 2 sheets to fit pan top and bottom Bottom sheet is larger than first and should cover the pan with some dough hanging over the sides Top sheet is a little larger than pan Oil pan and add cornmeal then add bottom sheet and have some hang over Mix inside ingredients all together Add inside ingredients to pan, put top dough on and fold over bottom sheet edges with top sheet to form crust Make holes in the top to let air escape Top generously with olive oil Bake until golden brown 35/40 min.</description></item><item><title>Veal and Peas</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-and-peas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-and-peas/</guid><description>Ingredients 1-2 lbs. veal shoulder steak, cut into pieces 2 T. Olive oil 1 onion, chopped Rosemary, salt, pepper 1/2 c. Wine 1 c. Beef stock 1 lb. frozen peas Directions Medium/High heat: brown meat in the oil Add onion and cook until done Add rosemary, salt and pepper Add wine and cook down Add stock a little at a time. Add frozen peas and cook until done</description></item><item><title>Veal Roast with Farfalle and Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-roast-with-farfalle-and-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-roast-with-farfalle-and-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 T. Olive oil 1 large onion, diced 2 lbs veal roast 1-2 cups red wine 1/2 c. Dried porcini mushrooms reconstituted in one cup hot water 8 ounces fresh mushrooms, sliced 1 t. Thyme 2 T. Butter Salt, pepper 1 lb farfalle pasta Directions Brown roast on all sides in the oil Add the onion and cook together Add the wine a little at a time Add the porcini and the water, a little at the time Add the thyme Cook for a good hr.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Gravy</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/vegetarian-gravy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/vegetarian-gravy/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/2 cup vegetable oil (we use olive oil) 1/3 cup chopped onion 5 cloves garlic, minced 1/2 cup all-purpose flour (use all-purpose gluten free if needed) 4 t. nutritional yeast 4 T. light soy sauce (use coconut aminos, tamari, or liquid aminos for gluten free) 2 cups vegetable broth (we usually need a bit more) 1/2 t dried sage 1/2 t salt 1/4 t ground black pepper Directions Heat oil in a medium saucepan over medium heat.</description></item><item><title>Walnut Wedding Cookies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter, room temp 1/3 cup powdered sugar, plus more for rolling cookies 2 t. vanilla 1/4 t. salt 2 cups pastry flour (sifted all purpose) 3/4 cup finely chopped toasted walnuts Directions Beat butter and sugar until fluffy Beat in vanilla, salt Stir in flour and walnuts Form 1&amp;quot; balls Bake 325 degrees, 20 minutes Cool just a little bit Roll in powdered sugar while still warm Refrigerate 1 hour Roll again</description></item><item><title>Wild Mushroom Ragu</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wild-mushroom-ragu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wild-mushroom-ragu/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/3 C. Olive oil 4 C. Mixed mushrooms Salt, pepper 2 cloves minced garlic 1 minced shallot 1 t. Rosemary 1 t. Oregano 1/2 c. Tomato sauce 1/4 c. Red wine 1/2 c. Veggie broth 1 T. Butter Chopped fresh parsley OR:
2 pounds mixed mushrooms, such as cremini, shiitake, and oyster 1 medium yellow onion 1 medium carrot 3 cloves garlic 2 tablespoons olive oil 1 teaspoon kosher salt, divided 1/4 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper 1/4 cup dry white wine 2 tablespoons tomato paste 1 (28-ounce) can diced tomatoes 1/2 cup water 1 bay leaf 2 sprigs fresh thyme 1 sprig fresh rosemary 1/4 teaspoon red pepper flakes 1 teaspoon balsamic vinegar Directions Serve over pasta or polenta</description></item><item><title>Wine</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wine/</guid><description>Description Grandpa Bellino&amp;rsquo;s wine; Rosa&amp;rsquo;s handwritten notes
Directions 10 cases muscat 2 cases zinfandel crush place in press strain in barrel leave 5&amp;quot; from top Continue filling with about 1 gal. After it boils (1 month) Cork it (40 days later) After 3-6 months place in bottles</description></item><item><title>‘Ncicirata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs 2 tablespoons sugar 2 tablespoons oil I used canola 1 teaspoon pure vanilla extract 2 tablespoons grappa limoncello or rum are also good choices 1/2 cup milk 1/8 teaspoon fine sea salt 1 teaspoon baking powder 3 1/4 cups all-purpose flour approximately vegetable oil for deep frying Honey Mixture 1 cup honey grated zest of a lemon sprinkles of your choice Directions In a medium sized bowl whisk together the eggs, sugar, oil, vanilla extract, grappa and milk.</description></item></channel></rss>