<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/</link><description>Recent content on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amaretti</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/amaretti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/amaretti/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 1/4 cups almond flour or very finely ground almonds, sifted 1 cup granulated sugar pinch salt 2 large egg whites 1/4 teaspoon lemon juice 1/2 teaspoon almond extract confectioners’ sugar, as needed Directions Preheat oven to 300 degrees F. Stack two matching, heavyweight, cookie sheets together. Line with parchment paper or a silicone baking mat. In a large bowl, whisk together almond flour, sugar and salt until evenly incorporated.</description></item><item><title>Boulevardier</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/boulevardier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/boulevardier/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 - 1.25 part Rye Whiskey (Bourbon for sweeter) 1 part Campari 1 part Sweet Vermouth Directions Combine over ice Stir Serve in chilled glass Garnish with orange peel</description></item><item><title>Cannarìcuwi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</guid><description>Description pasta arrotolata della lunghezza di un pollice cotta in olio bollente e ricoperta di miele</description></item><item><title>Cantuccini</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</guid><description>Description Biscotti
Ingredients 2 cups+1 tablespoon) all-purpose flour sifted 3/4 cup + 1 tablespoon) granulated sugar 1 tablespoon honey 1 teaspoon baking powder 1 teaspoon grated orange zest or lemon zest 1 teaspoon amaretto or 1/2 teaspoon almond extract (optional) 2 eggs ½ cup raw unpeeled almonds Directions Preheat the oven to 180 degrees C (356 degrees F). In a large bowl, combine the dry ingredients. Add the eggs, honey, orange zest, amaretto and mix all the ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Caponata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/caponata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/caponata/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/4 c. Olive oil 1 large carrot chopped (1/2”) 1 large onion chopped 2-3 stalks celery chopped 1 firm eggplant, peeled and chopped 1 can petite diced tomatoes 1 can water or vegetable stock 2 T. Capers 2 T. Vinegar 4 oz black and/ or green sliced olives Parsley, chopped fine Directions Sauté carrot, onion and celery until soft Add eggplant and stir until all coated with oil mix Add tomatoes, water and cook over medium heat until very soft, about 20 min.</description></item><item><title>Castagnaccio</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g di farina di castagne 1 litro di acqua 50 g di zucchero di canna biologico (facoltativo) 150 g di uvetta 20 g circa di pinoli italiani ½ cucchiaio di semini di finocchietto 5 cucchiai di olio extravergine di oliva ligure sale fino marino Directions Sciacquate l&amp;rsquo;uva passa, e lasciatela in ammollo circa 30 minuti in acqua tiepida. In una terrina molto capiente versate tutta la farina di castagne setacciandola, in modo da non creare grumi.</description></item><item><title>Chestnut Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chestnut-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chestnut-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 lb. roasted chestnuts (2 cups) 1/2 c. pine nuts, toasted 1 c. sugar 4 eggs separated 10 T. butter, room temperature 1 t. vanilla 4 ounces semisweet chocolate Directions Preheat oven to 350 degrees. Butter an 8-inch springform pan and line the bottom with parchment or waxed paper. Butter the paper and flour the pan. In a large mixing bowl, beat the egg yolks and sugar until the mixture is pale and thick enough to leave a ribbon, 2 to 3 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Cranberry Relish</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-relish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-relish/</guid><description>Ingredients 1lb. Cranberries 1 orange, diced 1/3c. Sugar Directions Place in processor and process until well chopped</description></item><item><title>Cranberry Sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-sauce/</guid><description>Ingredients 1lb. Cranberries 1 orange, diced 1 piece of candied ginger 1 stick of cinnamon 1/3 c. Sugar 1c. Water Directions Place all in a saucepan and cover with water. Bring to boil and cook until cranberries pop. Cool and serve.</description></item><item><title>Crispi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 cups of flour 1 package of yeast 1T. salt 1-2 cups water Oil for frying Directions Mix as you would for making a pizza. This dough will be a lot stickier Let rise until doubled Dip your hands into a bowl of oil, shape a bit of dough into a round doughnut or ring and drop into a pan full of very hot oil until golden brown.</description></item><item><title>Easy Lasagne</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/easy-lasagne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/easy-lasagne/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 pkg chopped frozen spinach-thawed and squeezed of water 1 lb. ricotta 1/2 c. grated parmesan Salt, pepper 2 cups tomato sauce 1/2 lb. shredded mozzarella 1/2 pkg oven ready lasagne Directions Mix spinach, ricotta, grated cheese, salt, pepper and set aside Place a layer of sauce in an 8x8 baking dish Top with noodles, spinach mix, mozzarella and sauce Repeat until all used Cover with foil and bake for 30 min in 400 degree oven Remove foil and bake 10 more minutes</description></item><item><title>Farinata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 C. Garbanzo flour 1 C. Water 1 t. Salt 1 t. Pepper 1 t. Rosemary or other herb Oil Directions Whisk flour, water, salt, pepper, herbs and 1 T. Oil Refrigerate for 1-2 hrs Preheat a cast iron pan in 450 oven Pour 2+T. Oil in pan, add the batter and bake for 5-10min</description></item><item><title>French Onion Soup</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/french-onion-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/french-onion-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 T olive oil 3 or more onions, sliced 1 bouillon cube 4 cups water 1 T flour (optional) Directions Cook onions in oil until brown Add flour, bouillon cube, and water Bring to boil, then simmer for 1 hour Place 1 slice Italian bread topped with Swiss cheese in a bowl Top with soup</description></item><item><title>Frizzuli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/frizzuli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/frizzuli/</guid><description>Ingredients flour-one handful per person 2 eggs Water Directions None provided</description></item><item><title>Gnocchi Verdi: Spinach and Ricotta Gnocchi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gnocchi-verdi-spinach-and-ricotta-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gnocchi-verdi-spinach-and-ricotta-gnocchi/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 pkg frozen, chopped spinach, thawed, cooked (3 min. In micro) and water squeezed out 1 lb. ricotta cheese 1/2 cup grated Parmesan 1 cup flour Salt, pepper, nutmeg Directions To the cooked spinach, add all other ingredients. Form little balls about the size of a teaspoon Roll on flour sprinkled on a cutting board Cook in plenty of salted water They are done when they come to the top In a pan melt some butter, add a few leaves of sage and the cooked gnocchi Serve with more Parmesan cheese Alternative Mix together 1 10oz chopped frozen spinach: cooked, all water squeezed out and minced 1 lb of ricotta 1 lge egg 1/2 teaspoon nutmeg 1 teaspoon salt Fold in 4 Tablespoons Parmesan 1/2 c flour</description></item><item><title>Grandma Bellino's Meatballs</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-meatballs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-meatballs/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/2 lb. ground beef 1/2 lb. ground pork 1 T. Italian seasonings 1 egg 1/2 c. Grated cheese 1/2 c. Breadcrumbs Salt, pepper, diced garlic, chopped parsley Directions Mix all ingredients together Form medium size balls Fry or bake Add to tomato sauce and cook together Serve over pasta</description></item><item><title>Grandma Bellino's Pizza</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-pizza/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/grandma-bellino-s-pizza/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 C. Flour 1 pkg yeast (proof in 1/2 C. Warm water and 1/2 t. Sugar) 1 t. Salt 1 c. Warm water 1 red pepper, sliced thinly 1 large onion, sliced thinly 2 cloves garlic, sliced thinly 1 T. Italian seasonings salt, pepper, peperoncino 1/2 lb. shredded mozzarella Directions In a mixing bowl place the flour, salt and yeast mixture. Slowly add more water and knead until dough is nice and elastic.</description></item><item><title>Insalata Russa</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 1lb frozen peas 1lb frozen cubed carrots 2 large potatoes boiled and cubed Mayonnaise Directions Mix all together. Shape into oval and decorate with Olives, gerghins, capers, anchovies</description></item><item><title>Jan Hagel</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: Mom always made these for Christmas and everybody thought that they were Italian cookies, but I had found this recipe in a magazine when I was in high school and we always made them together. It’s a Swedish cookie.​​
Ingredients 1 1/2 c. flour ​3/4 c. sugar ​½ t. cinnamon ​½ c. butter ​1 egg ​1 egg white ​½ c. Slivered almonds Directions ​In large bowl combine flour, ½ c.</description></item><item><title>La Sardenaira</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 cups flour 2 cups of warm water 1 pk of yeast 3 T. oil 1 T. salt 1 t. sugar Original
Per la base:
500 grammi di farina di grano tenero tipo “0” ½ cubetto di lievito di birra 250 g di acqua Olio extravergine di oliva ligure 2 cucchiaini di sale fino marino (15/20 gr) 1 goccia di miele biologico Per il condimento</description></item><item><title>Lemon Chicken</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/lemon-chicken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/lemon-chicken/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 chicken breasts sliced crosswise and pounded until thin 4 T. Flour seasoned with salt and salt 2 T. Oil 1/4 c. lemon juice 1/2 c. Chicken stock Directions Dredge chicken in flour and fry in oil until golden Add lemon juice and stock and cook over low heat until done Serve with pan drippings and a slice of lemon</description></item><item><title>Negroni (Negroski)</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/negroni-negroski/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/negroni-negroski/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 part Gin (or Vodka) 1 part Campari 1 part Sweet Vermouth Directions Combine over ice Stir Serve in chilled glass Garnish with orange peel</description></item><item><title>Nonna's Chocolate Pudding</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-chocolate-pudding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-chocolate-pudding/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 Ripe avocado 2 t Cocoa powder 1 t honey or agave nectar 1/2 t water Directions Blend until smooth</description></item><item><title>Paolo's sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/dadssauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/dadssauce/</guid><description>Notes My mom always added butter at the end to give it a more velvety taste. I haven’t done it but it’s an option
Ingredients 1 large onion chopped and sautéed until translucent Olive oil (quello buono) 1 Large can of crushed tomatoes 1 Pomì of strained tomatoes Salt, pepper to taste Rosemary (fresh if possible) Directions Cover the bottom of the pan with oil on medium heat When oil is beginning to sizzle add the onion and rosemary.</description></item><item><title>Pasta with Ceci</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-with-ceci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-with-ceci/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. Olive oil 2 cloves garlic, chopped Dash of peperoncino 1 can petite diced tomatoes or 1 cup tomato sauce 1 can garbanzo beans Salt, pepper, oregano 1/2 lb. short pasta like farfalle 1/2 c. Grated Parmesan cheese Directions Sauté garlic in olive oil until golden Add. tomatoes, peperoncino, salt, pepper and oregano and cook Add beans and cook until soft Add some water as needed Add cooked pasta to the skillet and toss with cheese</description></item><item><title>Pat O'Brien's Hurricane</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pat-o-brien-s-hurricane/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pat-o-brien-s-hurricane/</guid><description>Ingredients 1oz vodka 1/4oz grenadine 1oz gin 1oz light rum 1/2oz 151 rum 1oz amaretto 1oz triple sec Grapefruit juice Pineapple juice</description></item><item><title>Pitte ’N Chiuse</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 C. Flour 3 T. Oil 1 t. Salt 1 C. Water In the meantime, chop 2 bunches Swiss Chards Add 1/2 to 1 C. Raisins Pinch of peperoncino  Salt and pepper Directions Mix together and let it rest covered Let it rest a good hr, at which time squeeze out any moisture Pinch off some dough and form a thin circle about 7-10 inches Place a dollop of Swiss chard, wet all around and fold like a turnover  Bake for 30 min in 400 degree oven</description></item><item><title>Potato Gnocchi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 medium potatoes, cooked and riced 1 t. Salt, 1 t. Pepper 1 egg 1 c. Flour Directions Cook the potatoes in their skin. Cool and rice Add the rest of ingredients to the potatoes Form a long rope of about a foot Cut rope every one inch Run each over a grater to form indentation; or use a fork Cook in plenty of salted water They are done when they come to the top Serve with any sauce</description></item><item><title>Pupuwignognuwu - Easter Babies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pupuwignognuwu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pupuwignognuwu/</guid><description>Description Easter babies
Ingredients 1c. Milk 1/2 stick of butter 1/2 c. Sugar 1 pkg of yeast 4 eggs 4 c. Flour  Egg wash (mix one egg with 1 T. water) Icing-optional (1 c. Confectioners sugar mixed with warm milk) Original:
1 kg.di farina, 1 cucchiaio raso di sale, 4 uova, 1 bicchiere di olio,1 bicchiere di vino bianco, 12 gr. di lievito di birra. Impastare tipo gnocchi, morbido, lasciar lievitare per alcune ore.</description></item><item><title>Raschiatelli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/raschiatelli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/raschiatelli/</guid><description>Ingredients Flour one handful per person Water Directions None provided</description></item><item><title>Sausage and Peppers</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sausage-and-peppers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sausage-and-peppers/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. Olive oil 1 red pepper, sliced 1 yellow pepper, sliced 1 large onion, sliced Salt, pepper 5-6 sausage links (I prefer hot Italian) Directions Sauté vegetable in oil with salt and pepper Remove vegetables from pan and add sausages Brown sausages on all sides Add the vegetables, some water, and cook over medium heat until sausages are done</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description></item><item><title>Spinach Ricotta Pie</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 frozen pie crusts - bake as directed 2 10 oz frozen chopped spinach, thawed and all water squeezed out 1 lb ricotta 1 can evaporated milk 3 eggs 1 T. instant dry onion 1/2 t salt 1/4 t pepper 1/4 t ground nutmeg 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Preheat oven, 350 degrees Mix ricotta with next 7 ingredients Add spinach Place in crusts and cook for 50 minutes, 350 degrees</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 3 medium size potatoes  4 tablespoon of extra-virgin olive oil  1 medium size onions, minced 1lb medium size white onions 2 eggs, lightly beaten 3 tablespoons freshly grated parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon of marjoram leaves, minced 1 tablespoon of fresh Italian (flat) parsley, minced fine sea salt to taste pepper to taste 1 cup fine unflavoured bread crumbs Directions Wash the potatoes, put them with their peel into a pot filled with cold water and boil for about 35 minutes or until tender.</description></item><item><title>Sugo di Carne</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sugo-di-carne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sugo-di-carne/</guid><description>Ingredients 4T. Olive oil 2 cloves of garlic 1lb. Beef chuck short ribs- boneless 1lb. Pork shoulder country style ribs-boneless 1 28oz. Tomato purée 2T. Tomato paste 1T. Salt 1t. Pepper 2 sprigs rosemary Directions Brown garlic in the oil and remove when golden Add the meat and sauté until nicely browned Add all other ingredients and bring to a boil Turn to simmer and cook for at least 2 hrs.</description></item><item><title>Taralli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taralli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taralli/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 1 cup flour 120 grams 2 tablespoons olive oil 30 grams 4 tablespoons white wine 60 grams 1/2 teaspoon salt 2 1/2 grams 1/2 tablespoon fennel seeds if desired I&amp;rsquo;m sure sesame seeds would work too Directions In a large bowl whisk flour, salt and fennel seeds together, add olive oil and wine combine with a wooden spoon, place on a flat surface and knead for approximately 10 minutes until dough is smooth and elastic.</description></item><item><title>test</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/books/family/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/books/family/</guid><description>test Main</description></item><item><title>Tiramisu</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs, separated 1/2 cup sugar 1/2 lb. light or fat-free ricotta 1/3 cup heavy cream 1 pkg lady fingers 2 T rum 1/3 cup espresso 1 bar chocolate, 3 oz Directions Combine egg yolks and sugar. Beat until light Mix in 1 cup ricotta, combined with cream Blend in rum Beat egg whites until stiff. Fold into cheese mixture. Refrigerate Shred chocolate over top</description></item><item><title>Torroncino</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: This recipe comes from Adriana Scalora a former student of mine at LTHS (1979-2003). I’ve made them for Christmas ever since she gave me the recipe in the late 80s.
Ingredients 1/4 c. honey 1 ½ c. sugar 1 lb. Skinless slivered almonds, toasted 2 T. sesame seeds, toasted 1 t. diced orange peel Directions Bring honey to a boil Add sugar and stir until dissolved Add orange peel and almonds and cook stirring for 2-3 min.</description></item><item><title>Torta di Patate</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</guid><description>Description Torta di Patate, without sfoglia: Potato pie, recipe without the crust. Use the crust from Torta verde
Ingredients 4 medium potatoes boiled in their skin, cooled and riced 1 egg Salt, pepper, nutmeg 1/2 c. Grated Parmesan 1/2 c. Bread crumbs 1/2 c. Milk Directions Mix all together Place 1/2 mixture in a greased pie pan Top with sliced ham and/or mozzarella, if using Top with remaining potato mixture Top with a film of olive oil Bake for 45 min.</description></item><item><title>Torta Verde</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough:
1 cup warm water 3/4 cup oil  1 T salt Inside:
2 big bunches Swiss chard chopped and steamed 4 zucchini shredded 1/2 bag frozen or 2 cans artichokes chopped fine 3 eggs 1 cup Parmesan cheese Handful of rice Directions Dough:
Mix until smooth dough forms Roll out 2 sheets to fit pan top and bottom Oil pan and add cornmeal then add bottom sheet and have some hang over Mix inside ingredients all together Add inside ingredients to pan, put top dough on and fold over edges to form crust Top generously with olive oil and bake until golden brown 35/40 min.</description></item><item><title>Veal and Peas</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-and-peas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-and-peas/</guid><description>Ingredients 1-2 lbs. veal shoulder steak, cut into pieces 2 T. Olive oil 1 onion, chopped Rosemary, salt, pepper 1/2 c. Wine 1 c. Beef stock 1 lb. frozen peas Directions Brown meat in the oil, add onion and cook until done Add rosemary, salt and pepper Add wine and when cooked down, add stock a little at a time. Add frozen peas and cook until done</description></item><item><title>Veal Roast with Farfalle and Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-roast-with-farfalle-and-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veal-roast-with-farfalle-and-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 T. Olive oil 1 large onion, diced 2 lbs veal roast 1-2 cups red wine 1/2 c. Dried porcini mushrooms reconstituted in one cup hot water 8 ounces fresh mushrooms, sliced 1 t. Thyme 2 T. Butter Salt, pepper 1 lb farfalle pasta Directions Brown roast on all sides in the oil Add the onion and cook together Add the wine a little at a time Add the porcini and the water, a little at the time Add the thyme Cook for a good hr.</description></item><item><title>Walnut Wedding Cookies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter, room temp 1/3 cup powdered sugar, plus more for rolling cookies 2 t. vanilla 1/4 t. salt 2 cups pastry flour (sifted all purpose) 3/4 cup finely chopped toasted walnuts Directions Beat butter and sugar until fluffy Beat in vanilla, salt Stir in flour and walnuts Form 1&amp;quot; balls Bake 325 degrees, 20 minutes Cool just a little bit Roll in powdered sugar while still warm Refrigerate 1 hour Roll again</description></item><item><title>‘Ncicirata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs 2 tablespoons sugar 2 tablespoons oil I used canola 1 teaspoon pure vanilla extract 2 tablespoons grappa limoncello or rum are also good choices 1/2 cup milk 1/8 teaspoon fine sea salt 1 teaspoon baking powder 3 1/4 cups allpurpose flour approximately vegetable oil for deep frying Directions In a medium sized bowl whisk together the eggs, sugar, oil, vanilla extract, grappa and milk.</description></item></channel></rss>