<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Christmas on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/christmas/</link><description>Recent content in Christmas on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black Bean Tamale Pie</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/black-bean-tamale-pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/black-bean-tamale-pie/</guid><description>Ingredients Black Bean Chili Filling: 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 onion, chopped 1 clove garlic, minced 1 bell pepper, chopped 1 medium zucchini, chopped 1 tablespoon chili powder 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper (use more if you want more heat) 1 teaspoon ground cumin 1 teaspoon ground coriander 1 15. oz. can black beans, drained and rinsed 1 15 oz. diced tomatoes with juice Vegan Cornmeal Topping: 3/4 cup ground cornmeal 1/4 cup cup whole-wheat flour (use gluten-free flour blend for gluten free option) 1/2 teaspoon baking powder 1/4 cup canola oil or olive oil 1 tablespoon maple syrup 3/4 cup unsweetened soymilk or other unsweetened non-dairy milk 1 teaspoon apple cider vinegar 1 4oz.</description></item><item><title>Brandacujun</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</guid><description>Description Dried cod (stockfish) with potatoes.
Ingredients 1 1/2 lb. Salted, dried cod 4 russet/white potatoes, diced 2 garlic cloves, crushed 3 tbsp minced parsley 1/4-1/2 cup olive oil salt to taste Directions Soak the fish in water for 3 days, changing the water twice a day; this removes some of the salt and softens the dry fish Cut into pieces Boil potatoes Before they’re done, add fish.</description></item><item><title>Brown Butter Sugar Cookies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brown-butter-sugar-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brown-butter-sugar-cookies/</guid><description>Description https://www.barleyandsage.com/brown-butter-sugar-cookies/
Ingredients 1 cup unsalted brown butter, room temperature 1 ¼ cup granulated sugar ¼ cup light brown sugar 2 large eggs, room temperature 2 teaspoons vanilla extract ½ teaspoon almond extract, optional ½ teaspoon lemon juice, optional 2 cups all purpose flour 1 teaspoon baking soda ½ teaspoon kosher salt sparkling sugar, for topping Directions Using a stand or hand mixer, cream together the brown butter, granulated sugar, and brown sugar until smooth and creamy.</description></item><item><title>Buche de Noel</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/buche-de-noel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/buche-de-noel/</guid><description>Description Christmas log
Ingredients 6 egg whites (see Note) ¾ cup sugar, 6 egg yolks ½ cup unsweetened cocoa 1½ teaspoons vanilla extract Dash salt Confectioners' sugar FILLING
1½ cups heavy cream, chilled ½ cup confectioners' sugar ¼ cup unsweetened cocoa 2 teaspoons instant coffee 1 teaspoon vanilla extract Candied cherries, angelica Note: Let egg whites warm to room temperature, about 1 hour. You may make the Chocolate Log a week ahead, then freeze it, wrapped in foil.</description></item><item><title>Cannarìculi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</guid><description>Description pasta arrotolata della lunghezza di un pollice cotta in olio bollente e ricoperta di miele
Ingredients 1 cup flour 1 egg 1/2 cup white wine 1/2 cup oil (light vegetable oil, like sunflower) 1/2 t. baking powder 2 t. sugar Directions Mix ingredients Make a long and round rope Cut 1&amp;quot; pieces and fry in oil Roll in honey when still hot</description></item><item><title>Christmas Pasta</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/christmas-pasta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/christmas-pasta/</guid><description>NEED RECIPE## Ingredients
Tomato sauce 1 lb. salted cod, soaked for three days; switch water twice a day 1 lb. Spaghetti cooked 1 cup breadcrumbs 1 T paprika Dash red pepper flakes salt and pepper to taste 1/2-1 cup raisins Directions To tomato sauce, add softened cod and raisins Cook until fish starts to fall apart Toast breadcrumbs in pan with olive oil, paprika, and red pepper In serving dish add breadcrumbs to spaghetti Then add sauce</description></item><item><title>Coffee Kranz</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough
1/2 lb. margarine 3 egg yolks 2 Tbsp sugar 1 t salt 1 package dry yeast 4 cups sifted flour 1 cup milk Cheese Filling (makes 3 cups)
2 large (8 oz) cream cheese 1 cup sugar 1 egg 1 t vanilla Directions For dough:
Combine all ingredients in order into one bowl Mix as for pie crust using a pastry cutter Add milk and mix (with hands) Cover and refrigerate over night Cheese filling:</description></item><item><title>Crispi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 cups of flour 1 package of yeast 1T. salt 1-2 cups water Oil for frying Directions Mix as you would for making a pizza. This dough will be a lot stickier Let rise until doubled Dip your hands into a bowl of oil, shape a bit of dough into a round doughnut or ring and drop into a pan full of very hot oil until golden brown.</description></item><item><title>Horseradish-Crusted Beef Tenderloin</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/horseradish-crusted-beef-tenderloin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/horseradish-crusted-beef-tenderloin/</guid><description>Description From Epicurious: https://www.epicurious.com/recipes/food/views/horseradish-crusted-beef-tenderloin-232147
Ingredients 1 (3 1/2-lb) trimmed center-cut beef tenderloin roast, tied 1 1/4 teaspoons salt 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 6 tablespoons olive oil 1 lb fresh horseradish, peeled and coarsely grated (1 cup; see cooks' note, below) 2 tablespoons Dijon mustard Directions Step 1 Put oven rack in middle position and preheat oven to 400°F.
Step 2 Pat tenderloin dry, then sprinkle with salt and pepper.</description></item><item><title>Jan Hagel</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: Mom always made these for Christmas and everybody thought that they were Italian cookies, but I had found this recipe in a magazine when I was in high school and we always made them together. It’s a Swedish (or maybe Dutch) cookie.​​
Ingredients 1 1/2 c. flour ​3/4 c. sugar ​½ t. cinnamon ​½ c. butter ​1 egg ​1 egg white ​½ c. slivered almonds Directions ​In large bowl combine flour, ½ c.</description></item><item><title>Ravioli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</guid><description>Ingredients DOUGH
2 cups all-purpose flour, plus more for dusting 1 teaspoon salt 3 large eggs, plus 1 for egg wash 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil Cornmeal, for dusting Gluten-free:
substitute gluten-free all-purpose flour add 2 tsp per cup of flour of Xantham gum (if not already in the flour you are using) 1 additional egg FILLING
Spinach and Ricotta Filling
1 lb chopped spinach Use frozen, microwave until thawed and squeeze all liquid out; almost dry 1 lb ricotta 1 egg 1/2 c.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Chestnuts</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/roasted-chestnuts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/roasted-chestnuts/</guid><description>Ingredients Raw chestnuts in shell
Directions Score/slit the chestnuts with a knife. Spread on a baking sheet 400 degrees til they’re done, stirring once, about 20-25 min done= slightly toasted, a little fragrant, starting to open</description></item><item><title>Royal Icing</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/royal-icing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/royal-icing/</guid><description>Description This is a short description
Ingredients 4 cups (480g) confectioners’ sugar, sifted (I use and recommend Domino brand); 3 Tablespoons meringue powder (not plain egg white powder) 9–10 Tablespoons room temperature water optional for decorating: gel food coloring Directions Pour confectioners’ sugar, meringue powder, and 9 Tablespoons of water into a large bowl. Using a hand mixer or a stand mixer fitted with a whisk attachment, beat icing ingredients together on high speed for 1.</description></item><item><title>Soft Cut-Out Sugar Cookies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/best-sugar-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/best-sugar-cookies/</guid><description>Description https://sallysbakingaddiction.com/best-sugar-cookies/
Ingredients 2 and 1/4 cups (281g) all-purpose flour (spooned &amp;amp; leveled), plus more as needed for rolling and work surface 1/2 teaspoon baking powder 1/4 teaspoon salt 3/4 cup (170g) unsalted butter, softened to room temperature 3/4 cup (150g) granulated sugar 1 large egg, at room temperature 2 teaspoons pure vanilla extract 1/4 or 1/2 teaspoon almond extract (optional, but makes the flavor outstanding)* Directions Whisk the flour, baking powder, and salt together in a medium bowl.</description></item><item><title>Torroncino</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: This recipe comes from Adriana Scalora a former student of mine at LTHS (1979-2003). I’ve made them for Christmas ever since she gave me the recipe in the late 80s.
Makes about 6 dozen.
Ingredients 1/4 c. honey 1 ½ c. sugar 1 lb. Skinless slivered almonds, toasted 2 T. sesame seeds, toasted 1 t. diced orange peel Directions Bring honey to a boil Add sugar and stir until dissolved Add orange peel and almonds and cook stirring for 2-3 min.</description></item><item><title>Walnut Wedding Cookies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter, room temp 1/3 cup powdered sugar, plus more for rolling cookies 2 t. vanilla 1/4 t. salt 2 cups pastry flour (sifted all purpose) 3/4 cup finely chopped toasted walnuts Directions Beat butter and sugar until fluffy Beat in vanilla, salt Stir in flour and walnuts Form 1&amp;quot; balls Bake 325 degrees, 20 minutes Cool just a little bit Roll in powdered sugar while still warm Refrigerate 1 hour Roll again</description></item><item><title>‘Ncicirata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicirata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicirata/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs 2 tablespoons sugar 2 tablespoons oil I used canola 1 teaspoon pure vanilla extract 2 tablespoons grappa limoncello or rum are also good choices 1/2 cup milk 1/8 teaspoon fine sea salt 1 teaspoon baking powder 3 1/4 cups all-purpose flour approximately vegetable oil for deep frying Honey Mixture 1 cup honey grated zest of a lemon sprinkles of your choice Directions In a medium sized bowl whisk together the eggs, sugar, oil, vanilla extract, grappa and milk.</description></item></channel></rss>