<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Christmas on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/christmas/</link><description>Recent content in Christmas on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brandacujun</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</guid><description>Description Dried cod (stockfish) with potatoes.
Ingredients Salted, dried cod 1 kg potatoes (about 7) 2 garlic cloves, crushed 3 tbsp minced parsley 1 tbsp olive oil Directions Soak the fish in water for 24 hours, changing the water every few hours; this removes some of the salt and softens the dry fish Cut into pieces</description></item><item><title>Cannarìculi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cannaricuwi/</guid><description>Description pasta arrotolata della lunghezza di un pollice cotta in olio bollente e ricoperta di miele
Ingredients 1 cup flour 1 egg 1/2 cup white wine 1/2 cup oil (light vegetable oil, like sunflower) 1/2 t. baking powder 2 t. sugar Directions Mix ingredients Make a long and round rope Cut 1&amp;quot; pieces and fry in oil Roll in honey when still hot</description></item><item><title>Coffee Kranz</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough
1/2 lb. margarine 3 egg yolks 2 Tbsp sugar 1 t salt 1 package dry yeast 4 cups sifted flour 1 cup milk Cheese Filling (makes 3 cups)
2 large (8 oz) cream cheese 1 cup sugar 1 egg 1 t vanilla Directions For dough:
Combine all ingredients in order into one bowl Mix as for pie crust using a pastry cutter Add milk and mix (with hands) Cover and refrigerate over night Cheese filling:</description></item><item><title>Crispi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 cups of flour 1 package of yeast 1T. salt 1-2 cups water Oil for frying Directions Mix as you would for making a pizza. This dough will be a lot stickier Let rise until doubled Dip your hands into a bowl of oil, shape a bit of dough into a round doughnut or ring and drop into a pan full of very hot oil until golden brown.</description></item><item><title>Jan Hagel</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: Mom always made these for Christmas and everybody thought that they were Italian cookies, but I had found this recipe in a magazine when I was in high school and we always made them together. It’s a Swedish (or maybe Dutch) cookie.​​
Ingredients 1 1/2 c. flour ​3/4 c. sugar ​½ t. cinnamon ​½ c. butter ​1 egg ​1 egg white ​½ c. Slivered almonds Directions ​In large bowl combine flour, ½ c.</description></item><item><title>Ravioli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 cups all-purpose flour, plus more for dusting 1 teaspoon salt 3 large eggs, plus 1 for egg wash 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil Cornmeal, for dusting FILLING
1lb chopped, frozen spinach, microwaved and squeezed almost dry 1lb ricotta 1 egg 1/2 c. grated cheese Salt, pepper Dash of nutmeg Directions Combine the flour and salt on a flat work surface; shape into a mound and make a well in the center.</description></item><item><title>Torroncino</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torroncino/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: This recipe comes from Adriana Scalora a former student of mine at LTHS (1979-2003). I’ve made them for Christmas ever since she gave me the recipe in the late 80s.
Ingredients 1/4 c. honey 1 ½ c. sugar 1 lb. Skinless slivered almonds, toasted 2 T. sesame seeds, toasted 1 t. diced orange peel Directions Bring honey to a boil Add sugar and stir until dissolved Add orange peel and almonds and cook stirring for 2-3 min.</description></item><item><title>Walnut Wedding Cookies</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/walnut-wedding-cookies/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter, room temp 1/3 cup powdered sugar, plus more for rolling cookies 2 t. vanilla 1/4 t. salt 2 cups pastry flour (sifted all purpose) 3/4 cup finely chopped toasted walnuts Directions Beat butter and sugar until fluffy Beat in vanilla, salt Stir in flour and walnuts Form 1&amp;quot; balls Bake 325 degrees, 20 minutes Cool just a little bit Roll in powdered sugar while still warm Refrigerate 1 hour Roll again</description></item><item><title>‘Ncicirata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs 2 tablespoons sugar 2 tablespoons oil I used canola 1 teaspoon pure vanilla extract 2 tablespoons grappa limoncello or rum are also good choices 1/2 cup milk 1/8 teaspoon fine sea salt 1 teaspoon baking powder 3 1/4 cups all-purpose flour approximately vegetable oil for deep frying Honey Mixture 1 cup honey grated zest of a lemon sprinkles of your choice Directions In a medium sized bowl whisk together the eggs, sugar, oil, vanilla extract, grappa and milk.</description></item></channel></rss>