<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sides on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/sides/</link><description>Recent content in Sides on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/sides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Caponata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/caponata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/caponata/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/4 c. Olive oil 1 large carrot chopped (1/2”) 1 large onion chopped 2-3 stalks celery chopped 1 firm eggplant, peeled and chopped 1 can petite diced tomatoes 1 can water or vegetable stock 2 T. Capers 2 T. Vinegar 4 oz black and/ or green sliced olives Parsley, chopped fine Directions Sauté carrot, onion and celery until soft Add eggplant and stir until all coated with oil mix Add tomatoes, water and cook over medium heat until very soft, about 20 min.</description></item><item><title>Castagnaccio</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g di farina di castagne 1 litro di acqua 50 g di zucchero di canna biologico (facoltativo) 150 g di uvetta 20 g circa di pinoli italiani ½ cucchiaio di semini di finocchietto 5 cucchiai di olio extravergine di oliva ligure sale fino marino Directions Sciacquate l&amp;rsquo;uva passa, e lasciatela in ammollo circa 30 minuti in acqua tiepida. In una terrina molto capiente versate tutta la farina di castagne setacciandola, in modo da non creare grumi.</description></item><item><title>Cranberry Relish</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-relish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-relish/</guid><description>Ingredients 1lb. Cranberries 1 orange, diced 1/3c. Sugar Directions Place in processor and process until well chopped</description></item><item><title>Cranberry Sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cranberry-sauce/</guid><description>Ingredients 1lb. Cranberries 1 orange, diced 1 piece of candied ginger 1 stick of cinnamon 1/3 c. Sugar 1c. Water Directions Place all in a saucepan and cover with water. Bring to boil and cook until cranberries pop. Cool and serve.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 3 medium size potatoes  4 tablespoon of extra-virgin olive oil  1 medium size onions, minced 1lb medium size white onions 2 eggs, lightly beaten 3 tablespoons freshly grated parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon of marjoram leaves, minced 1 tablespoon of fresh Italian (flat) parsley, minced fine sea salt to taste pepper to taste 1 cup fine unflavoured bread crumbs Directions Wash the potatoes, put them with their peel into a pot filled with cold water and boil for about 35 minutes or until tender.</description></item></channel></rss>