<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sauces on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/sauces/</link><description>Recent content in Sauces on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/sauces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emeril's Essence Creole Seasoning</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/emeril-s-essense/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/emeril-s-essense/</guid><description>Description Creole Seasoning (also referred to as Bayou Blast)
Ingredients 2 1/2 tablespoons paprika 2 tablespoons salt 2 tablespoons garlic powder 1 tablespoon black pepper 1 tablespoon onion powder 1 tablespoon cayenne pepper 1 tablespoon dried oregano 1 tablespoon dried thyme</description></item><item><title>Paolo's sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/dads-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/dads-sauce/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 large onion chopped and sautéed until translucent Olive oil (quello buono) 1 Large can of crushed tomatoes 1 Pomì of strained tomatoes Salt, pepper to taste Rosemary (fresh if possible) Directions Cover the bottom of the pan with oil on medium heat When oil is beginning to sizzle add the onion and rosemary. Stir so onion and rosemary don’t burn. Add tomatoes salt and pepper. Bring everything to a boil and then lower heat and simmer for 40/45 minutes and voilà Keep the can to add water to the sauce as needed.</description></item><item><title>Pesto</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</guid><description>Description Pesto can be made and frozen. If frozen do not add cheese or nuts; you can add those later, if you want.
Ingredients Basil Olive oil Garlic, multiple cloves Salt Parmesan cheese (optional) Pine nuts (optional) Directions Mix together in food processor Use right away or store in refrigerator (add oil to cover); or freeze When ready to use, warm up, add to pasta with a square of butter.</description></item><item><title>Pickled Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-onions/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 red onion, thinly sliced 1 c. White vinegar 1 c. Water 1 t. Sea salt 1 T. Honey Dash of red pepper flakes (optional) Peppercorns (optional) Directions Place sliced onions in a jar Combine the rest of the ingredients in a saucepan and bring to a boil Fill jar, cool and refrigerate</description></item><item><title>Ranch dressing</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ranch-dressing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ranch-dressing/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup mayonnaise 6 Tablespoons milk (use dairy free if needed; we used Oat) 2 teaspoons apple cider vinegar 1 Tablespoon + 1 teaspoon dried parsley 1 teaspoon dried chives 1 teaspoon garlic powder 1 teaspoon onion powder 1/2 teaspoon dried dill salt and pepper Directions Add all ingredients into a bowl then whisk until smooth. Add more milk to thin dressing out if desired. Store in the refrigerator for 1-2 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Sugo di Carne</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sugo-di-carne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sugo-di-carne/</guid><description>Ingredients 4T. Olive oil 2 cloves of garlic 1lb. Beef chuck short ribs- boneless 1lb. Pork shoulder country style ribs-boneless 1 28oz. Tomato purée 2T. Tomato paste 1T. Salt 1t. Pepper 2 sprigs rosemary Directions Brown garlic in the oil and remove when golden Add the meat and sauté until nicely browned Add all other ingredients and bring to a boil Turn to simmer and cook for at least 2 hrs.</description></item><item><title>Taco Seasoning</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taco-seasoning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taco-seasoning/</guid><description>Ingredients ​1 tbsp chili powder 1 tbsp sea salt 1 tbsp smoked paprika 1 tbsp cumin 1 tbsp onion powder 1 tbsp garlic powder 1 tbsp oregano ½ tbsp black pepper</description></item><item><title>Taco Seasoning - nightshade free</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taco-seasoning-nightshade-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/taco-seasoning-nightshade-free/</guid><description>Description Found this recipe when eliminating inflammatory foods. It&amp;rsquo;s really good on shrimp for tacos.
Ingredients 2 TB garlic powder 2 TB onion powder 2 TB ground turmeric 1 tsp ground ginger 1 tsp ground cinnamon 1 tsp dried oregano 1 tsp sea salt Directions Combine all seasonings in a glass container with a lid Shake well until combined Notes Originally from Clean Eating Veggie Girl: https://cleaneatingveggiegirl.</description></item><item><title>Tartar Sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tartar-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tartar-sauce/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup real Mayonnaise 1 cup dill pickles, finely chopped 1 Tbsp dill, fresh or frozen, OR 1 tbsp finely chopped fresh parsley 1 tsp lemon juice 1 tsp sugar 1/4 tsp black pepper, freshly ground 2 Tbsp onion, finely chopped, optional Directions Combine all ingredients in a bowl and stir to combine. Add more lemon juice or pickles if desired. Notes https://natashaskitchen.com/tartar-sauce-recipe/
SG notes: We don&amp;rsquo;t use the sugar and usually add more lemon.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Gravy</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/vegetarian-gravy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/vegetarian-gravy/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/2 cup vegetable oil (we use olive oil) 1/3 cup chopped onion 5 cloves garlic, minced 1/2 cup all-purpose flour (use all-purpose gluten free if needed) 4 t. nutritional yeast 4 T. light soy sauce (use coconut aminos, tamari, or liquid aminos for gluten free) 2 cups vegetable broth (we usually need a bit more) 1/2 t dried sage 1/2 t salt 1/4 t ground black pepper Directions Heat oil in a medium saucepan over medium heat.</description></item><item><title>Wild Mushroom Ragu</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wild-mushroom-ragu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wild-mushroom-ragu/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/3 C. Olive oil 4 C. Mixed mushrooms Salt, pepper 2 cloves minced garlic 1 minced shallot 1 t. Rosemary 1 t. Oregano 1/2 c. Tomato sauce 1/4 c. Red wine 1/2 c. Veggie broth 1 T. Butter Chopped fresh parsley OR:
2 pounds mixed mushrooms, such as cremini, shiitake, and oyster 1 medium yellow onion 1 medium carrot 3 cloves garlic 2 tablespoons olive oil 1 teaspoon kosher salt, divided 1/4 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper 1/4 cup dry white wine 2 tablespoons tomato paste 1 (28-ounce) can diced tomatoes 1/2 cup water 1 bay leaf 2 sprigs fresh thyme 1 sprig fresh rosemary 1/4 teaspoon red pepper flakes 1 teaspoon balsamic vinegar Directions Serve over pasta or polenta</description></item></channel></rss>