<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Desserts on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/desserts/</link><description>Recent content in Desserts on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/desserts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buche de Noel</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/buche-de-noel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/buche-de-noel/</guid><description>Ingredients 6 egg whites (see Note) ¾ cup sugar, 6 egg yolks ½ cup unsweetened cocoa 1½ teaspoons vanilla extract Dash salt Confectioners' sugar FILLING
1½ cups heavy cream, chilled ½ cup confectioners' sugar ¼ cup unsweetened cocoa 2 teaspoons instant coffee 1 teaspoon vanilla extract Candied cherries, angelica Note: Let egg whites warm to room temperature, about 1 hour. You may make the Chocolate Log a week ahead, then freeze it, wrapped in foil.</description></item><item><title>Cantuccini</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</guid><description>Description Biscotti
Ingredients 2 cups+1 tablespoon) all-purpose flour sifted 3/4 cup + 1 tablespoon) granulated sugar 1 tablespoon honey 1 teaspoon baking powder 1 teaspoon grated orange zest or lemon zest 1 teaspoon amaretto or 1/2 teaspoon almond extract (optional) 2 eggs ½ cup raw unpeeled almonds Directions Preheat the oven to 180 degrees C (356 degrees F). In a large bowl, combine the dry ingredients. Add the eggs, honey, orange zest, amaretto and mix all the ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Cenci</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cenci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cenci/</guid><description>Description Mardi Gras dessert
Ingredients 1 3/4 cups (225 g) flour 2 tablespoons unsalted butter 1/3 cup confectioners sugar 2 eggs 1 tablespoon brandy A pinch of salt More confectioner’s sugar for dusting Oil for deep frying Directions Make a fairly stiff dough with these ingredients, kneading it thoroughly, and adding more flour if it comes out too soft. Flour it and let it rest, covered tightly with plastic wrap, for about an hour.</description></item><item><title>Cherry Cheesecake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cherry-cheesecake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cherry-cheesecake/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 8oz pkg cream cheese 3/4 c. sugar 2 T. flour 1/2 t. salt 3 eggs, slightly beaten 1 c. sour cream 1/4 c. lemon juice 1 t. vanilla 1 can (21 oz) cherry pie filling Directions Preheat oven to 350 In 8-9 inch square pan, mash cream cheese with a fork until very soft Add sugar, flour, salt and blend well Add remaining ingredients except pie filling Mix briskly with fork until thoroughly blended Scrape down sides of pan Bake 350 degrees, 45 minutes or until pick inserted in center comes out clean Cool in pan on rack Spread with pie filling Chill Notes From Woman&amp;rsquo;s Day 1981</description></item><item><title>Chestnut Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chestnut-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chestnut-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 lb. roasted chestnuts (2 cups) 1/2 c. pine nuts, toasted 1 c. sugar 4 eggs separated 10 T. butter, room temperature 1 t. vanilla 4 ounces semisweet chocolate Directions Preheat oven to 350 degrees. Butter an 8-inch springform pan and line the bottom with parchment or waxed paper. Butter the paper and flour the pan. In a large mixing bowl, beat the egg yolks and sugar until the mixture is pale and thick enough to leave a ribbon, 2 to 3 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Coffee Kranz</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/coffee-kranz/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough
1/2 lb. margarine 3 egg yolks 2 Tbsp sugar 1 t salt 1 package dry yeast 4 cups sifted flour 1 cup milk Cheese Filling (makes 3 cups)
2 large (8 oz) cream cheese 1 cup sugar 1 egg 1 t vanilla Directions For dough:
Combine all ingredients in order into one bowl Mix as for pie crust using a pastry cutter Add milk and mix (with hands) Cover and refrigerate over night Cheese filling:</description></item><item><title>Flourless Chocolate Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/flourless-chocolate-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/flourless-chocolate-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients ½ cup water ¼ tsp sea salt ¾ cup granulated sugar 18 oz (2 ¼ cups) bittersweet chocolate chips (or chopped chocolate)* 1 cup salted butter, room temperature or Earth’s Balance 6 eggs, room temperature 1 tsp pure vanilla extract Directions Preheat oven to 300 degrees F. Grease one 9” round cake pan (or glass pie plate) and set aside. (Note: I always cut a piece of parchment paper into a circle with “handles” and place it on the bottom of the pan.</description></item><item><title>Italian Pear Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/italian-pear-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/italian-pear-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 9 Tbsp unsalted butter at room temperature 9 Tbsp white sugar 2 large eggs 7 Tbsp all-purpose flour 3.5 oz ground almonds 1/2 tsp baking powder 3 medium pears ripe, peeled, cored and halved 1.7 oz flaked almonds Icing sugar for garnish Directions
Pre-heat oven to 375° F. Grease an 8-inch springform pan and line the bottom with a round of parchment paper. Set aside. Prepare pears, by peeling, coring and cutting in half.</description></item><item><title>Jan Hagel</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/jan-hagel/</guid><description>Description Rosa’s notes: Mom always made these for Christmas and everybody thought that they were Italian cookies, but I had found this recipe in a magazine when I was in high school and we always made them together. It’s a Swedish (or maybe Dutch) cookie.​​
Ingredients 1 1/2 c. flour ​3/4 c. sugar ​½ t. cinnamon ​½ c. butter ​1 egg ​1 egg white ​½ c. Slivered almonds Directions ​In large bowl combine flour, ½ c.</description></item><item><title>King Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/king-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/king-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 roll frozen bread dough, thawed 8 ounces cream cheese, softened 1 cup powdered sugar 1 teaspoon lemon extract For the Icing: 1-1/2 cups confectioner’s sugar 3 tablespoons milk (more if needed but stir this amount first, you’ll be surprised how far this goes!) 1 tsp clear butter or vanilla flavoring Directions On floured surface, roll out your dough to a rectangle of about 10 x 18 inches.</description></item><item><title>Nonna's Butter Cake</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-butter-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-butter-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 2c. Flour 1c. Butter 2c. Sugar (1 cup) 1 beaten egg Dash of salt Sliced almonds Directions Keep half the beaten egg for top Knead all ingredients into smooth paste Butter a pie pan or spring form pan Press dough into it Brush with rest of beaten egg Press almonds on top Bake 30min. at 350 Questions: why is 2 c sugar followed by (1 cup)?</description></item><item><title>Nonna's Chocolate Pudding</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-chocolate-pudding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-chocolate-pudding/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 Ripe avocado 2 t Cocoa powder 1 t honey or agave nectar 1/2 t water Directions Blend until smooth in food processor</description></item><item><title>Peach Cobbler</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/peach-cobbler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/peach-cobbler/</guid><description>Ingredients 1/4-1/2 c. sugar 1 c. Bisquick 1 egg 1/4 c. milk or water 1 can peaches Topping:
2 T. Bisquick 1 T. butter 2 T. brown sugar Directions Mix dough Add peach slices Add topping Bake 350, 20-30 minutes Notes This cobbler is Rosa&amp;rsquo;s recipe, using bisquick. It can be made with other fruit, like blueberries.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Chestnuts</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/roasted-chestnuts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/roasted-chestnuts/</guid><description>Ingredients Raw chestnuts in shell
Directions Score/slit the chestnuts with a knife. Spread on a baking sheet 400 degrees til they’re done, stirring once, about 20-25 min done= slightly toasted, a little fragrant, starting to open</description></item><item><title>Tiramisu</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs, separated 1/2 cup sugar 1/2 lb. light or fat-free ricotta 1/3 cup heavy cream 1 pkg lady fingers 2 T rum 1/3 cup espresso 1 bar chocolate, 3 oz Directions Combine egg yolks and sugar. Beat until light Mix in 1 cup ricotta, combined with cream Blend in rum Beat egg whites until stiff. Fold into cheese mixture. Refrigerate Shred chocolate over top</description></item><item><title>‘Ncicirata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ncicrata/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 large eggs 2 tablespoons sugar 2 tablespoons oil I used canola 1 teaspoon pure vanilla extract 2 tablespoons grappa limoncello or rum are also good choices 1/2 cup milk 1/8 teaspoon fine sea salt 1 teaspoon baking powder 3 1/4 cups all-purpose flour approximately vegetable oil for deep frying Honey Mixture 1 cup honey grated zest of a lemon sprinkles of your choice Directions In a medium sized bowl whisk together the eggs, sugar, oil, vanilla extract, grappa and milk.</description></item></channel></rss>