<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Needs Work on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/needs-work/</link><description>Recent content in Needs Work on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/needs-work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brandacujun</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</guid><description>Description Dried cod (stockfish) with potatoes.
Ingredients Salted, dried cod 1 kg potatoes (about 7) 2 garlic cloves, crushed 3 tbsp minced parsley 1 tbsp olive oil Directions Soak the fish in water for 24 hours, changing the water every few hours; this removes some of the salt and softens the dry fish Cut into pieces</description></item><item><title>Cantuccini</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cantuccini/</guid><description>Description Biscotti
Ingredients 2 cups+1 tablespoon) all-purpose flour sifted 3/4 cup + 1 tablespoon) granulated sugar 1 tablespoon honey 1 teaspoon baking powder 1 teaspoon grated orange zest or lemon zest 1 teaspoon amaretto or 1/2 teaspoon almond extract (optional) 2 eggs ½ cup raw unpeeled almonds Directions Preheat the oven to 180 degrees C (356 degrees F). In a large bowl, combine the dry ingredients. Add the eggs, honey, orange zest, amaretto and mix all the ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Foccacia</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/foccacia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/foccacia/</guid><description>Description Almost no-knead foccacia, developed by David based on Grandma Giordano&amp;rsquo;s recipe (that wasn&amp;rsquo;t written down)
Ingredients 7 1/2 cups flour, 1/2 bread, 1/2 all purpose 1 tsp yeast 3 cups water 1 T salt Biga (old dough), about 1/2 cup. Skip if you don&amp;rsquo;t have Oil/salt for top Directions Preheat to 450 Mix flour, yeast, biga, water Add salt Knead until dough comes together, should be tacky Coat in oil and let rise overnight (8-24 hours) Stretch dough in jelly roll pan (or round) Let rise 1-2 hours Using hands, push dimples into dough, almost through to the pan Spray with water Coat in oil and sprinkle salt Put in oven (on tiles preferably) Add ice to a metal pan on floor of oven (for steam) Drop temp to 400 Bake 20-25 minutes</description></item><item><title>Frizzuli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/frizzuli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/frizzuli/</guid><description>Ingredients flour-one handful per person 2 eggs Water Directions None provided</description></item><item><title>Hummus</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/hummus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/hummus/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 can chick peas 2 cloves garlic lemon juice Oil or tahini Cumin Paprika Salt Directions Mix in food processor Add water to thin if necessary Variations
Add roasted red peppers Use white beans</description></item><item><title>Pesto</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</guid><description>Description Pesto can be made and frozen. If frozen do not add cheese or nuts; you can add those later, if you want.
Ingredients Basil Olive oil Garlic, multiple cloves Salt Parmesan cheese (optional) Pine nuts (optional) Directions Mix together in food processor Use right away or store in refrigerator (add oil to cover); or freeze When ready to use, warm up, add to pasta with a square of butter.</description></item><item><title>Pickled Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients water vinegar button mushrooms Directions Boil 1/2 water and 1/2 vinegar Add button mushrooms for 5 minutes Drain Cool mushrooms with lemons and peppercorns Place in jars Fill with vinegar Questions:
sliced lemons? How many? Do you put the lemons in the jars? I don&amp;rsquo;t remember lemons. White vinegar? Fill with vinegar - new vinegar, the vinegar/water mix? How many peppercorns? Black peppercorns? Amounts?</description></item><item><title>Raschiatelli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/raschiatelli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/raschiatelli/</guid><description>Ingredients Flour one handful per person Water Directions None provided</description></item><item><title>Ravioli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Rosette</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/rosette/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/rosette/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 1/2 c. flour 2 eggs 2 T sugar Directions Mix, roll flat Cut in ribbon, form in rosettes Fry in oil Top with honey and ground nuts QUESTIONS: how much honey? what type of nuts? What&amp;rsquo;s a rosette - a spiral? Do we have a pic?</description></item><item><title>Torta Verde</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough:
3 cups flour 1 cup warm water 3/4 cup oil 1 T salt Inside:
2 big bunches Swiss chard chopped and steamed. Can substitute spinach 4 small-med zucchini, shredded 1/2 bag frozen or 2 cans artichokes chopped fine 3 eggs 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese (or Romano) Handful of rice Directions Dough:
Mix until smooth dough forms Flour surface to roll out dough; divide dough Roll out 2 sheets to fit pan top and bottom Bottom sheet is larger than first and should cover the pan with some dough hanging over the sides Top sheet is a little larger than pan Oil pan and add cornmeal then add bottom sheet and have some hang over Mix inside ingredients all together Add inside ingredients to pan, put top dough on and fold over bottom sheet edges with top sheet to form crust Make holes in the top to let air escape Top generously with olive oil Bake until golden brown 35/40 min.</description></item><item><title>Wine</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wine/</guid><description>Description Grandpa Bellino&amp;rsquo;s wine; Rosa&amp;rsquo;s handwritten notes
Directions 10 cases muscat 2 cases zinfandel crush place in press strain in barrel leave 5&amp;quot; from top Continue filling with about 1 gal. After it boils (1 month) Cork it (40 days later) After 3-6 months place in bottles</description></item></channel></rss>