<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dinner on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/dinner/</link><description>Recent content in Dinner on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/dinner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black bean quesadillas</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/black-bean-quesadillas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/black-bean-quesadillas/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 cans black beans 1 yellow onion, sliced 2 poblano peppers, thinly sliced 2 tsp garlic powder 2 tsp cumin 2 tsp chili (or less, to taste) tortillas shredded cheese Directions Halve, deseed, and thinly slice poblano crosswise into strips Halve, peel, and thinly slice onion Add olive oil (or butter) to medium pot, medium-high heat Add beans and their liquid Add spices, and big pinch of salt (and pepper if you want) Bring bean mixture to a boil, then reduce to low simmer Cook until thickened, 3-4 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Brazilian Stew</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brazilian-stew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brazilian-stew/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 tablespoon oil 1 medium onion, chopped 2 cloves garlic, minced 2 sweet potatoes, peeled, diced 1 large red bell pepper, diced 1 cans diced tomatoes 1 hot green chili pepper, diced 2 cups vegetable stock plus 1 1/2 cups of water 2 cans black beans Serve and top with: 1 mango, peeled and diced 1/4 cup chopped fresh cilantro 1 lime (or whatever you want) Directions Cook onion, garlic, sweet potato and bell pepper until soft.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Piccata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chicken-piccata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chicken-piccata/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 large boneless and skinless chicken breasts, halved horizontally to make 4 2 tablespoons flour (all purpose or plain) 2 tablespoons finely grated fresh Parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon salt Cracked pepper For The Sauce:
Light spray of cooking oil 1 tablespoon olive oil 2 teaspoons butter (or oil) 2 tablespoons minced garlic 1 1/4 cup chicken broth (stock) 1/2 cup milk (full fat or 2% &amp;ndash; or use reduced fat cream or heavy cream) 1/2 cup finely grated fresh Parmesan cheese 2 tablespoons capers (plus 2 tablespoons extra to garnish) 1 teaspoon cornstarch (cornflour) mixed with 1 tablespoon of water 2-3 tablespoons lemon juice &amp;ndash; juice of 1 lemon (adjust to your tastes) 2 tablespoons fresh parsley Directions Lightly spray pan/skillet with a light coating of cooking oil spray and heat over medium-hight heat.</description></item><item><title>Chili - Sweet Potato and Black Bean</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chili-sweet-potato-and-black-bean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chili-sweet-potato-and-black-bean/</guid><description>Ingredients Olive oil Medium onion, diced 2 garlic cloves, minced 1 large sweet potato, peeled and diced Large can (28 oz) diced tomatoes 2 cans black beans 2 cups water 2 T mild chili powder (or 1 if too spicy) 2 tsp paprika 2 tsp cumin 1 tsp salt Directions Saute onion in oil until transparent, 3-4 minutes Add garlic and sweet potato, 2 minutes Add spices, stir and let coat sweet potatoes Add tomatoes, beans, water Bring to a boil Simmer uncovered, 20-25 minutes</description></item><item><title>Cornbread Stuffing</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cornbread-stuffing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cornbread-stuffing/</guid><description>Description Aunt Donna&amp;rsquo;s dressing, ish, without the meat.
Ingredients 8 cups cornbread cut into 1/2 inch pieces 1 loaf white bread (made fine) 3 cups vegetable stock 1 Tbs olive oil 1 yellow onion, finely chopped 1 celery stalk, finely chopped 1 carrot, finely chopped 2 tablespoons black pepper 4 tablespoons ground sage 1 egg Directions Preheat oven to 400 degrees F. Butter a 13-by-9 inch baking dish.</description></item><item><title>Egg-fried Cauliflower Rice</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/egg-fried-cauliflower-rice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/egg-fried-cauliflower-rice/</guid><description>Description AIP
Ingredients 3 tablespoons extra virgin olive oil or avocado oil 2 garlic cloves, crushed 2 teaspoons grated ginger 1 pound mixed stir fry veggies (any combination of broccoli florets, sliced carrots, snow peas, sliced mushrooms, sliced bell pepper and/or onion wedges; save prep time by using pre-cut options) (we use frozen) 8 ounces frozen cooked and peeled prawns/shrimp, thawed 1 12-ounce package of Riced Cauliflower or Broccoli, frozen 1/8 teaspoon salt 3 eggs 3 teaspoons toasted sesame oil, divided 2 tablespoons coconut aminos 2 spring onions, sliced 2 teaspoons sesame seeds Directions Whisk eggs with 1 teaspoon of sesame oil until frothy.</description></item><item><title>Fettuccine with Shrimp</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/fettuccine-with-shrimp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/fettuccine-with-shrimp/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. Olive oil 1 medium onion sliced thinly Dash of peperoncino 1 can petite diced tomatoes 1/3 c. White wine Salt, pepper, rosemary 1 lb. shrimp (8-10 per person, depending on size) 1/2 lb fettuccine, cooked al dente Basil Directions Sauté onion in oil until transparent Add peperoncino, tomatoes and wine Cook down Add salt, pepper, rosemary and shrimp Cook until shrimp is pink Add this to cooked pasta and serve Top with basil or parsley</description></item><item><title>Gnocchi Verdi: Spinach and Ricotta Gnocchi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gnocchi-verdi-spinach-and-ricotta-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/gnocchi-verdi-spinach-and-ricotta-gnocchi/</guid><description>Description Spinach and ricotta gnocchi with butter and sage sauce
Ingredients 1 pkg frozen, chopped spinach, thawed, cooked (3 minutes in microwave) and water squeezed out 1 lb. ricotta cheese 1 egg 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese 3/4 cup flour 1 tsp salt 1/2 tsp nutmeg 4 T unsalted butter 1T fresh sage (dried can be substituted) Directions Mix together spinach, ricotta, egg, nutmeg and salt Fold in 4 Tablespoons Parmesan and 1/2 c flour Spread 1/4 c flour on a plate Drop 1/2 t.</description></item><item><title>One Pot Enchilada</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/one-pot-enchilada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/one-pot-enchilada/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup quinoa 1 can black beans 1 sweet potato, 1/2&amp;quot; pieces 2 cups corn (can be frozen) 1 can diced tomatoes 1 can/packet enchilada sauce (10 oz) 1/2 cup water (we usually need more, probably closer to a cup) 2 cups kale or spinach (optional) 1/2 cup shredded cheese (optional) Seasoning: 1 tsp chili powder 1 tsp cumin 1/2 tsp paprika 1/4 tsp onion powder 1/4 tsp garlic powder salt to taste Directions Put all in a pan/pot Bring to boil Reduce to simmer Cover Cook 20 min or until quinoa is done, stirring occasionally.</description></item><item><title>Pan-Seared Cod with Lemon-Caper Pan Sauce</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pan-seared-cod-with-lemon-caper-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pan-seared-cod-with-lemon-caper-sauce/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 white fish fillets, (each 5 to 6 ounce) such as Pacific cod, lingcod, or rockfish Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper ½ cup all-purpose flour for dusting (gluten-free) 1 large egg, beaten 2 tablespoons extra virgin olive oil 3 tablespoons unsalted butter, divided 1 large garlic clove, thinly sliced 2 tablespoons small capers, drained 1 tablespoon freshly squeezed lemon juice ½ teaspoon finely grated lemon zest 2 tablespoons chopped fresh flat-leaf parsley Crusty bread for serving Directions Prep the Fish Sprinkle the fish generously with salt and let sit at room temperature for 10 minutes or refrigerate for up to 1 hour.</description></item><item><title>Pasta alla Puttanesca</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-alla-puttanesca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-alla-puttanesca/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 T. oil 4 cloves garlic, minced 1/4 c. chopped olives 1/4 c. capers 1 t. red pepper flakes 1 can tuna 1 can diced tomatoes Juice of 1/2 lemon zest of lemon Parsley 1/2 lb pasta Directions no directions included Notes David and Stephanie make this with spaghetti squash; no tuna or lemon. We use kalamata olives.</description></item><item><title>Pasta con Panna, Prosciutto, e Piselli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-con-panna-prosciutto-e-piselli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pasta-con-panna-prosciutto-e-piselli/</guid><description>Description Pasta with cream, ham/prosciutto, and peas
Ingredients 1 lb spaghetti 1 c. diced ham 1 pk. frozen peas 1 stick butter 1 quart half and half 1 c cheese salt pepper Directions Melt butter, cook ham and peas in butter Add cream Cook spaghetti Add spaghetti to cream mixture, cook while stirring Toss with 1 c. cheese, salt, pepper to taste</description></item><item><title>Peanut Noodles</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/peanut-noodles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/peanut-noodles/</guid><description>Ingredients Peanut sauce
1/2 cup natural peanut butter 1/3 cup tamari or coconut aminos 1 TB garlic powder 1 tsp ginger powder 1 TB sesame oil 1 TB honey or syrup 1 TB lime juice 1/2 cup warm water (add last) The rest
8 ounces spaghetti noodles or rice noodles (use brown rice ramen noodles) 1 cup shelled edamame 1 cup shredded red cabbage 1 cup shredded carrots 1/2 cup chopped cucumbers 1 red bell pepper, seeded and thinly sliced 2 green onions, chopped 1/4 cup chopped cilantro 1/4 cup chopped peanuts Directions Make the Peanut Sauce: In a small/medium bowl, whisk together all sauce ingredients until smooth.</description></item><item><title>Red Lentil Soup</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/red-lentil-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/red-lentil-soup/</guid><description>Description Warm Lentil soup fixes all ailments.
Ingredients 1 cup red lentils 2 carrots 1 onion 1 box of vegetable broth (4 cups) 1 tsp cumin 2 tsp turmeric 1/2 tsp salt (hot pepper if you like hot pepper) Directions rinse lentils dice vegetables cook onion until soft add vegetables and cook for a few minutes add spices and cook until fragrant Add rinsed lentils, stir add broth Bring everything to a boil then simmer for ~1 hour Grind using immersion blender or leave chunky Serve with drizzle of olive oil and/or balsamic vinegar (optional)</description></item><item><title>Spiced Butternut Squash Soup with Celeriac and Apple</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/butternut-celeriac-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/butternut-celeriac-soup/</guid><description>Description This is a short description
Ingredients 1 white onion, sliced 500g butternut squash, peeled and diced 500g celeriac, peeled and diced 2 apples, peeled and diced 1 litre vegetable stock (about 4 cups) 2 tsp dried sage 1/2 tsp ground nutmeg 1–2 tsp dried chilli flakes Salt and pepper to taste Directions Heat a large saucepan or casserole pot to a medium-low heat. Add the onions and saute for 8-10 minutes until the onions are soft and translucent.</description></item><item><title>Sweet Potato Tacos</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-tacos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-tacos/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 cups sweet potatoes, peeled and cut into 1/2-inch cubes from 2 sweet medium potatoes 1 Tbsp extra virgin olive oil 1 Tbsp taco seasoning 1 (15 oz) can black beans, drained and rinsed 3 cups quick slaw (recipe below) 6-8 (6 or 8-inch) corn tortillas, warmed 2 oz goat cheese crumbled, optional Quick Slaw:
2 cups finely shredded, red cabbage 2 Tbsp lime, juiced from 1 lime 1/2 tsp kosher salt 1/3 cup roughly chopped cilantro Taco Seasoning</description></item><item><title>Veggie Ramen</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veggieramen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veggieramen/</guid><description>Description Easy ramen that is filled with goodness.
Ingredients 4 hard boiled eggs 1 cup sweet yellow onion, sliced ~8 ounces shittake mushrooms 1 cup cabbage, thinly sliced 4 garlic cloves 2 large carrots 1 tablespoon toasted sesame oil 1 tablespoon olive oil 8 ounces dry ramen noodles 4 cups vegetable broth 4 tablespoons miso paste, divided 1 tablespoon mirin 1 tablespoon soy sauce ¼ cup coconut milk (optional, for creamy broth) 2 cups spinach leaves any other veggies that look good Directions Get all veggies cut, slice mushrooms, slice onions, chop garlic, thinly slice onions, matchstick carrots in a large pot boil water for cooking ramen noodles, cook ramen noodles as directed in a large pot over medium high heat add olive oil and sesame oil cook onion until transparent add garlic cook until just brown (30 seconds) add broth, 3 tbsp miso, mirin, mushrooms, and carrots cook until tender about 10 minutes add remaining veggies until cabbage and spinach are wilted.</description></item></channel></rss>