<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Appetizers on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/appetizers/</link><description>Recent content in Appetizers on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/appetizers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Castagnaccio</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g di farina di castagne 1 litro di acqua 50 g di zucchero di canna biologico (facoltativo) 150 g di uvetta 20 g circa di pinoli italiani ½ cucchiaio di semini di finocchietto 5 cucchiai di olio extravergine di oliva ligure sale fino marino Directions Sciacquate l&amp;rsquo;uva passa, e lasciatela in ammollo circa 30 minuti in acqua tiepida. In una terrina molto capiente versate tutta la farina di castagne setacciandola, in modo da non creare grumi.</description></item><item><title>Crispi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 cups of flour 1 package of yeast 1T. salt 1-2 cups water Oil for frying Directions Mix as you would for making a pizza. This dough will be a lot stickier Let rise until doubled Dip your hands into a bowl of oil, shape a bit of dough into a round doughnut or ring and drop into a pan full of very hot oil until golden brown.</description></item><item><title>Farinata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 c. Garbanzo flour 1 c. Water 1 t. Salt 1 t. Pepper 1 t. Rosemary or other herb Oil Directions Whisk flour, water, salt, pepper, herbs and 1 T. Oil Refrigerate for 1-2 hrs Preheat a cast iron pan in 450 oven Pour 2+T. Oil in pan, add the batter and bake for 5-10min</description></item><item><title>Insalata Russa</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</guid><description>Description Grandma Giordano made this for special occasions, especially Easter.
Ingredients 1 lb frozen peas, cooked according to package 1 lb frozen cubed carrots, cooked according to package 2 large potatoes boiled and cubed Mayonnaise Directions Mix all together. Shape into oval and decorate with Olives, gherkins, capers, anchovies</description></item><item><title>La Sardenaira</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 cups flour 2 cups of warm water 1 pk of yeast 3 T. oil 1 T. salt 1 t. sugar Directions Mix the above together and let rise. Place dough in a pan and top with the following 1 can peeled tomatoes Oregano Garlic in their peel anchovies (optional) Olives - (taggiasche); substitute black cured Capers (optional) Olive oil Bake in a hot oven (475) until done (15 min) Notes Original recipe in Italian:</description></item><item><title>Pickled Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients water vinegar button mushrooms Directions Boil 1/2 water and 1/2 vinegar Add button mushrooms for 5 minutes Drain Cool mushrooms with lemons and peppercorns Place in jars Fill with vinegar Questions:
sliced lemons? How many? Do you put the lemons in the jars? I don&amp;rsquo;t remember lemons. White vinegar? Fill with vinegar - new vinegar, the vinegar/water mix? How many peppercorns? Black peppercorns? Amounts?</description></item><item><title>Pitte ’N Chiuse</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 C. Flour 3 T. Oil 1 t. Salt 1 C. Water In the meantime, chop 2 bunches Swiss Chards Add 1/2 to 1 C. Raisins Pinch of peperoncino  Salt and pepper Directions Mix together and let it rest covered Let it rest a good hr, at which time squeeze out any moisture Pinch off some dough and form a thin circle about 7-10 inches Place a dollop of Swiss chard, wet all around and fold like a turnover  Bake for 30 min in 400 degree oven</description></item><item><title>Spinach Ricotta Pie</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 frozen pie crusts - bake as directed 2 10 oz frozen chopped spinach, thawed and all water squeezed out 1 lb ricotta 1 can evaporated milk 3 eggs 1 T. instant dry onion 1/2 t salt 1/4 t pepper 1/4 t ground nutmeg 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Preheat oven, 350 degrees Mix ricotta with next 7 ingredients Add spinach Place in crusts and cook for 50 minutes, 350 degrees</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 3 medium size potatoes  4 tablespoon of extra-virgin olive oil  1 medium size onions, minced 1lb medium size white onions 2 eggs, lightly beaten 3 tablespoons freshly grated parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon of marjoram leaves, minced 1 tablespoon of fresh Italian (flat) parsley, minced fine sea salt to taste pepper to taste 1 cup fine unflavoured bread crumbs Directions Wash the potatoes, put them with their peel into a pot filled with cold water and boil for about 35 minutes or until tender.</description></item><item><title>Torta di Patate</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</guid><description>Description Torta di Patate, without sfoglia: Potato pie, recipe without the crust. Use the crust from Torta verde
Ingredients 4 medium potatoes boiled in their skin, cooled and riced 1 egg Salt, pepper, nutmeg 1/2 c. Grated Parmesan 1/2 c. Bread crumbs 1/2 c. Milk Directions Mix all together Place 1/2 mixture in a greased pie pan Top with sliced ham and/or mozzarella, if using Top with remaining potato mixture Top with a film of olive oil Bake for 45 min.</description></item><item><title>Torta Verde</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough:
3 cups flour 1 cup warm water 3/4 cup oil 1 T salt Inside:
2 big bunches Swiss chard chopped and steamed. Can substitute spinach 4 small-med zucchini, shredded 1/2 bag frozen or 2 cans artichokes chopped fine 3 eggs 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese (or Romano) Handful of rice Directions Dough:
Mix until smooth dough forms Flour surface to roll out dough; divide dough Roll out 2 sheets to fit pan top and bottom Bottom sheet is larger than first and should cover the pan with some dough hanging over the sides Top sheet is a little larger than pan Oil pan and add cornmeal then add bottom sheet and have some hang over Mix inside ingredients all together Add inside ingredients to pan, put top dough on and fold over bottom sheet edges with top sheet to form crust Make holes in the top to let air escape Top generously with olive oil Bake until golden brown 35/40 min.</description></item></channel></rss>