<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Appetizers on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/appetizers/</link><description>Recent content in Appetizers on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/appetizers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arancini</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/arancini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/arancini/</guid><description>Description Need a recipe</description></item><item><title>Buffalo Cauliflower</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/buffalo-cauliflower/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/buffalo-cauliflower/</guid><description>Description So yummy!
Ingredients Cauliflower:
1 large head cauliflower (about 2½ pounds), cut into medium and large florets (about 8 cups) 3 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil Kosher salt and black pepper Can also add: Garlic powder and paprika Buffalo Sauce:
4 tablespoons unsalted butter ⅓ cup Buffalo-style hot sauce (Frank&amp;rsquo;s Original) Directions Heat oven to 400 degrees, and place a rack close to the broiler and another in the middle of the oven.</description></item><item><title>Carciofi Sott'olio</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/carciofi-sott-olio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/carciofi-sott-olio/</guid><description>NEED RECIPE</description></item><item><title>Castagnaccio</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/castagnaccio/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g di farina di castagne 1 litro di acqua 50 g di zucchero di canna biologico (facoltativo) 150 g di uvetta 20 g circa di pinoli italiani ½ cucchiaio di semini di finocchietto 5 cucchiai di olio extravergine di oliva ligure sale fino marino Directions Sciacquate l&amp;rsquo;uva passa, e lasciatela in ammollo circa 30 minuti in acqua tiepida. In una terrina molto capiente versate tutta la farina di castagne setacciandola, in modo da non creare grumi.</description></item><item><title>Creole Shrimp Skewers</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/creole-shrimp-skewers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/creole-shrimp-skewers/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 tablespoons Creole Seasoning 6 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted 1 pound medium shrimp (30/40) peeled and deveined Directions Preheat the oven to 425 degrees F. Combine the Creole Seasoning and melted butter in a medium bowl. Whisk to combine. Place 3 tablespoons of this mixture in a shallow dish and reserve the remaining mixture for later. Skewer the shrimp on small 6 inch skewers, using 2-3 shrimp per skewer.</description></item><item><title>Crispi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/crispi/</guid><description>Ingredients 2-4 cups of flour 1 package of yeast 1T. salt 1-2 cups water Oil for frying Directions Mix as you would for making a pizza. This dough will be a lot stickier Let rise until doubled Dip your hands into a bowl of oil, shape a bit of dough into a round doughnut or ring and drop into a pan full of very hot oil until golden brown.</description></item><item><title>Farinata</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/farinata/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 c. Garbanzo flour 1 c. Water 1 t. Salt 1 t. Pepper 1 t. Rosemary or other herb Oil Directions Whisk flour, water, salt, pepper, herbs and 1 T. Oil Refrigerate for 1-2 hrs Preheat a cast iron pan in 450 oven Pour 2+T. Oil in pan, add the batter and bake for 5-10min</description></item><item><title>Fried Zucchini Flowers</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/fried-zucchini-flowers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/fried-zucchini-flowers/</guid><description>NEED RECIPE## Ingredients
Zucchini flowers, stamens removed Notes David and Stephanie&amp;rsquo;s note: This is the only reason we grow zucchini</description></item><item><title>Hummus</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/hummus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/hummus/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 can chick peas, drained 1-2 cloves garlic 1-2 T. lemon juice 1/4 c. Olive oil 1 T tahini (optional) Cumin (to taste, probably about 1-2 tsp) Paprika (to taste, probably 1 tsp) Salt to taste Directions Mix in food processor Add water to thin if necessary Notes You can use just olive oil, just tahini, or a mix Add roasted red peppers Use white beans</description></item><item><title>Insalata Russa</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</guid><description>Description Grandma Giordano made this for special occasions, especially Easter.
Ingredients 1 lb frozen peas, cooked according to package 1 lb frozen cubed carrots, cooked according to package 2 large potatoes boiled and cubed Mayonnaise Directions Mix all together. Shape into oval and decorate with Olives, gherkins, capers, anchovies</description></item><item><title>La Sardenaira</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 cups flour 2 cups of warm water 1 pk of yeast 3 T. oil 1 T. salt 1 t. sugar Directions Mix the above together and let rise. Place dough in a pan and top with the following 1 can peeled tomatoes Oregano Garlic in their peel anchovies (optional) Olives - (taggiasche); substitute black cured Capers (optional) Olive oil Bake in a hot oven (475) until done (15 min) Notes Original recipe in Italian:</description></item><item><title>Melanzane sotto Aceto</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/melanzane-sotto-aceto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/melanzane-sotto-aceto/</guid><description>Description Pickled Eggplant
Directions Peel, slice, and julienne eggplant Salt and leave for 24 hours Squeeze out liquid Boil 1/2 water, 1/2 white vinegar Put eggplants in water/vinegar mix for 24 hours Squeeze Mix/baste them with oil, sliced garlic, chopped celery, red pepper flakes, oregano, pepper (black peppercorns) Fill jars</description></item><item><title>Pickled Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pickled-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients water White vinegar button mushrooms (whole) Directions Boil 1/2 water and 1/2 white vinegar Add button mushrooms for 5 minutes Drain Cool mushrooms with lemons and peppercorns Place in jars (not the lemons) Fill with white vinegar to cover Notes We think the lemons are sliced and used only during cooling. They do not go in the jars.</description></item><item><title>Pitte ’N Chiuse</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pitte-n-chiuse/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 C. Flour 3 T. Oil 1 t. Salt 1 C. Water In the meantime, chop 2 bunches Swiss Chards Add 1/2 to 1 C. Raisins Pinch of peperoncino Salt and pepper Directions Mix together and let it rest covered Let it rest a good hr, at which time squeeze out any moisture Pinch off some dough and form a thin circle about 7-10 inches Place a dollop of Swiss chard, wet all around and fold like a turnover Bake for 30 min in 400 degree oven</description></item><item><title>Spinach Ricotta Pie</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/spinach-ricotta-pie/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 frozen pie crusts - bake as directed 2 10 oz frozen chopped spinach, thawed and all water squeezed out 1 lb ricotta 1 can evaporated milk 3 eggs 1 T. instant dry onion 1/2 t salt 1/4 t pepper 1/4 t ground nutmeg 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Preheat oven, 350 degrees Mix ricotta with next 7 ingredients Add spinach Place in crusts and cook for 50 minutes, 350 degrees</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Artichokes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-artichokes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-artichokes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Stuffed Mushrooms</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-mushrooms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-mushrooms/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 1/2 lb. baby Bella mushrooms 2 tbsp. butter 2 cloves garlic, minced 1/4 c. breadcrumbs Kosher salt Freshly ground black pepper 1/4 c. freshly grated Parmesan, plus more for topping 4 oz. cream cheese, softened 2 tbsp. freshly chopped parsley, plus more for garnish 1 tbsp. freshly chopped thyme Directions Clean the mushrooms and remove the stems Chop the stems and sauté in butter and garlic Add to the rest of ingredients and stuff the mushrooms with this mix Place the mushrooms in a baking dish and bake in 350 oven for 20-30 min Shortcut: Add a cup of spinach artichoke Parmesan spread to the sautéed stems.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</guid><description>Description Cipolle Ripiene
Ingredients 3 medium size potatoes 4 tablespoon of extra-virgin olive oil 1 medium size onions, minced 1lb medium size white onions 2 eggs, lightly beaten 3 tablespoons freshly grated parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon of marjoram leaves, minced 1 tablespoon of fresh Italian (flat) parsley, minced fine sea salt to taste pepper to taste 1 cup fine unflavoured bread crumbs Directions Wash the potatoes, put them with their peel into a pot filled with cold water and boil for about 35 minutes or until tender.</description></item><item><title>Sweet and Spicy Pecans</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sweet-and-spicy-pecans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sweet-and-spicy-pecans/</guid><description>Ingredients Cooking spray 2 cups pecans, pieces or halves 1 tablespoon unsalted butter 3 tablespoons dark brown sugar 1 1/2 tablespoons maple syrup 1 1/2 teaspoons kosher salt 3/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon Directions Gather the ingredients Position a rack in the center of the oven and heat to 350 F. Prepare a baking sheet by lining it with aluminum foil and spraying the foil with cooking spray.</description></item><item><title>Torta di Patate</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-di-patate/</guid><description>Description Torta di Patate, without sfoglia: Potato pie, recipe without the crust. Use the crust from Torta verde
Ingredients 4 medium potatoes boiled in their skin, cooled and riced 1 egg Salt, pepper, nutmeg 1/2 c. Grated Parmesan 1/2 c. Bread crumbs 1/2 c. Milk Directions Mix all together Place 1/2 mixture in a greased pie pan Top with sliced ham and/or mozzarella, if using Top with remaining potato mixture Top with a film of olive oil Bake for 45 min.</description></item><item><title>Torta Verde</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough:
3 cups flour 1 cup warm water 1/2 cup oil 1 T salt Inside:
2 big bunches Swiss chard chopped and sauted. Can substitute spinach 1 small chopped onion sautéed with chard (optional) 4 small-med zucchini, shredded, squeeze with salt in cheese cloth 1/2 bag frozen or 2 cans artichokes chopped fine 3 eggs 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese (or Romano)(rosa says 1/2 cup) 1/2 cup of rice (minute rice is less fussy) Directions Dough:</description></item></channel></rss>