<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Soups and Stews on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/soups-and-stews/</link><description>Recent content in Soups and Stews on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/categories/soups-and-stews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brazilian Stew</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brazilian-stew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brazilian-stew/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 tablespoon oil 1 medium onion, chopped 2 cloves garlic, minced 2 sweet potatoes, peeled, diced 1 large red bell pepper, diced 1 cans diced tomatoes 1 hot green chili pepper, diced 2 cups vegetable stock plus 1 1/2 cups of water 2 cans black beans Serve and top with: 1 mango, peeled and diced 1/4 cup chopped fresh cilantro 1 lime (or whatever you want) Directions Cook onion, garlic, sweet potato and bell pepper until soft.</description></item><item><title>Chili - Sweet Potato and Black Bean</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chili-sweet-potato-and-black-bean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/chili-sweet-potato-and-black-bean/</guid><description>Ingredients Olive oil Medium onion, diced 2 garlic cloves, minced 1 large sweet potato, peeled and diced Large can (28 oz) diced tomatoes 2 cans black beans 2 cups water 2 T mild chili powder (or 1 if too spicy) 2 tsp paprika 2 tsp cumin 1 tsp salt Directions Saute onion in oil until transparent, 3-4 minutes Add garlic and sweet potato, 2 minutes Add spices, stir and let coat sweet potatoes Add tomatoes, beans, water Bring to a boil Simmer uncovered, 20-25 minutes</description></item><item><title>Cozy Butternut, Sweet Potato, and Red Lentil Stew</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cozy-butternut-sweet-potato-and-red-lentil-stew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/cozy-butternut-sweet-potato-and-red-lentil-stew/</guid><description>Description From Oh She Glows: Butternut squash, red lentils, and sweet potato are wrapped in a lightly sweet and creamy coconut and tomato broth accented with spicy notes of turmeric, cumin, chili powder, cayenne, and garlic. Apple cider vinegar provides a tangy brightness to bring everything together. This stew tastes better the next day once the flavors have had a chance to mingle.
Ingredients FOR THE STEW: 2 tablespoons (30 mL) extra-virgin olive oil 1 medium onion, diced (about 2 cups/280 g) 3 to 4 large garlic cloves, minced 3 cups (400 g) peeled, seeded, and diced butternut squash* 1 large sweet potato (450 g), peeled and diced (2 1/2 cups/340 g)* 3 cups (750 mL) low-sodium vegetable broth 1 (14-ounce/398 mL) can diced tomatoes 1 (14-ounce/398 mL) can light coconut milk 1/2 cup (100 g) dried red lentils, rinsed** 3 tablespoons (45 mL) tomato paste 1 1/2 teaspoons ground turmeric 1 1/2 teaspoons ground cumin 1/2 teaspoon chili powder 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper, or more if you like heat Fine sea salt, to taste (I use 1 1/2 teaspoons pink salt) Freshly ground black pepper, to taste 3 teaspoons (15 mL) apple cider vinegar, or to taste 1 bunch chard, stemmed and finely chopped*** OPTIONAL ACCOMPANIMENTS: Fresh cilantro or parsley, minced Cooked rice Garlic powder and chili powder Directions To a large pot, add the oil, onion, and garlic.</description></item><item><title>French Onion Soup</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/french-onion-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/french-onion-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 T olive oil 3 or more onions, sliced 1 bouillon cube 4 cups water 1 T flour (optional) Directions Cook onions in oil until brown Add flour, bouillon cube, and water Bring to boil, then simmer for 1 hour Place 1 slice Italian bread topped with Swiss cheese in a bowl Top with soup</description></item><item><title>Minestrone</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/minestrone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/minestrone/</guid><description>NEED RECIPE</description></item><item><title>Nonna Soup</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/nonna-s-soup/</guid><description>Description This is basically a minestrone; it&amp;rsquo;s a made-up soup based on soup Rosa (Nonna to Beatrice) makes. We call it Nonna soup to identify it as the one Rosa has made for us.
Ingredients Onion, diced 2 clove garlic 2 carrots, chopped 1 zucchini, chopped 1 white potato (or parsnip) 1 can diced tomatoes 1 can beans - chickpeas or white Salt/pepper to taste 4 cups (1 box) vegetable broth (or whatever broth you want) Directions Saute onion until translucent Add garlic Add veggies, add salt as you go Add tomatoes, beans, and broth Boil and then lower to simmer, 15-20 minutes until veg are done Use immersion blender to blend a bit (not smooth) Notes Additions:</description></item><item><title>One Pot Enchilada</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/one-pot-enchilada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/one-pot-enchilada/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 cup quinoa 1 can black beans 1 sweet potato, 1/2&amp;quot; pieces 2 cups corn (can be frozen) 1 can diced tomatoes 1 can/packet enchilada sauce (10 oz) 1/2 cup water (we usually need more, probably closer to a cup) 2 cups kale or spinach (optional) 1/2 cup shredded cheese (optional) Seasoning: 1 tsp chili powder 1 tsp cumin 1/2 tsp paprika 1/4 tsp onion powder 1/4 tsp garlic powder salt to taste Directions Put all in a pan/pot Bring to boil Reduce to simmer Cover Cook 20 min or until quinoa is done, stirring occasionally.</description></item><item><title>Red Lentil Soup</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/red-lentil-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/red-lentil-soup/</guid><description>Description Warm Lentil soup fixes all ailments.
Ingredients 1 cup red lentils 2 carrots 1 onion 1 box of vegetable broth (4 cups) 1 tsp cumin 2 tsp turmeric 1/2 tsp salt (hot pepper if you like hot pepper) Directions rinse lentils dice vegetables cook onion until soft add vegetables and cook for a few minutes add spices and cook until fragrant Add rinsed lentils, stir add broth Bring everything to a boil then simmer for ~1 hour Grind using immersion blender or leave chunky Serve with drizzle of olive oil and/or balsamic vinegar (optional)</description></item><item><title>Spiced Butternut Squash Soup with Celeriac and Apple</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/butternut-celeriac-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/butternut-celeriac-soup/</guid><description>Description This is a short description
Ingredients 1 white onion, sliced 500g butternut squash, peeled and diced 500g celeriac, peeled and diced 2 apples (i use Granny Smiths), peeled and diced 1 litre vegetable stock 2 tsp dried sage 1/2 tsp ground nutmeg 1–2 tsp dried chilli flakes Salt and pepper to taste Directions Heat a large saucepan or casserole pot to a medium-low heat. Add the onions and saute for 8-10 minutes until the onions are soft and translucent.</description></item><item><title>Veggie Ramen</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veggieramen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/veggieramen/</guid><description>Description Easy ramen that is filled with goodness.
Ingredients 4 hard boiled eggs 1 cup sweet yellow onion, sliced ~8 ounces shittake mushrooms 1 cup cabbage, thinly sliced 4 garlic cloves 2 large carrots 1 tablespoon toasted sesame oil 1 tablespoon olive oil 8 ounces dry ramen noodles 4 cups vegetable broth 4 tablespoons miso paste, divided 1 tablespoon mirin 1 tablespoon soy sauce ¼ cup coconut milk (optional, for creamy broth) 2 cups spinach leaves any other veggies that look good Directions Get all veggies cut, slice mushrooms, slice onions, chop garlic, thinly slice onions, matchstick carrots in a large pot boil water for cooking ramen noodles, cook ramen noodles as directed in a large pot over medium high heat add olive oil and sesame oil cook onion until transparent add garlic cook until just brown (30 seconds) add broth, 3 tbsp miso, mirin, mushrooms, and carrots cook until tender about 10 minutes add remaining veggies until cabbage and spinach are wilted.</description></item><item><title>Wedding Soup</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wedding-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/wedding-soup/</guid><description>Description Minestra con polpettine di pollo (Is this the wedding soup?)
Ingredients For soup:
1medium onion, chopped 2 stalks of celery, chopped 2 carrots, chopped 2 T. Oil 4 cups chicken stock Head of escarole (or substitute kale) Parmesan for serving For meatballs
1 lb. Ground chicken 1 egg 1/2 c. Breadcrumbs 1/2 c. Grated Parmesan 1 T. Chopped parsley Salt, pepper Directions Sauté onions, celery, and carrots in oil, until soft Add 4 cups chicken stock and bring to a boil.</description></item></channel></rss>