<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Northern Italy on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/northern-italy/</link><description>Recent content in Northern Italy on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/northern-italy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Insalata Russa</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</guid><description>Description Grandma Giordano made this for special occasions, especially Easter.
Ingredients 1 lb frozen peas, cooked according to package 1 lb frozen cubed carrots, cooked according to package 2 large potatoes boiled and cubed Mayonnaise Directions Mix all together. Shape into oval and decorate with Olives, gherkins, capers, anchovies</description></item><item><title>La Sardenaira</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 cups flour 2 cups of warm water 1 pk of yeast 3 T. oil 1 T. salt 1 t. sugar Directions Mix the above together and let rise. Place dough in a pan and top with the following 1 can peeled tomatoes Oregano Garlic in their peel anchovies (optional) Olives - (taggiasche); substitute black cured Capers (optional) Olive oil Bake in a hot oven (475) until done (15 min) Notes Original recipe in Italian:</description></item><item><title>Potato Gnocchi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 medium potatoes, cooked and riced 1 t. Salt, 1 t. Pepper 1 egg 1 c. Flour Directions Cook the potatoes in their skin. Cool and rice Add the rest of ingredients to the potatoes Form a long rope of about a foot Cut rope every one inch Run each over a grater to form indentation; or use a fork Cook in plenty of salted water They are done when they come to the top Serve with any sauce</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 3 medium size potatoes  4 tablespoon of extra-virgin olive oil  1 medium size onions, minced 1lb medium size white onions 2 eggs, lightly beaten 3 tablespoons freshly grated parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon of marjoram leaves, minced 1 tablespoon of fresh Italian (flat) parsley, minced fine sea salt to taste pepper to taste 1 cup fine unflavoured bread crumbs Directions Wash the potatoes, put them with their peel into a pot filled with cold water and boil for about 35 minutes or until tender.</description></item><item><title>Torta Verde</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough:
3 cups flour 1 cup warm water 3/4 cup oil 1 T salt Inside:
2 big bunches Swiss chard chopped and steamed 4 zucchini shredded 1/2 bag frozen or 2 cans artichokes chopped fine 3 eggs 1 cup Parmesan cheese Handful of rice Directions Dough:
Mix until smooth dough forms Roll out 2 sheets to fit pan top and bottom Oil pan and add cornmeal then add bottom sheet and have some hang over Mix inside ingredients all together Add inside ingredients to pan, put top dough on and fold over edges to form crust Top generously with olive oil and bake until golden brown 35/40 min.</description></item></channel></rss>