<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Northern Italy on Recipes</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/northern-italy/</link><description>Recent content in Northern Italy on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/tags/northern-italy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brandacujun</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/brandacujun/</guid><description>Description Dried cod (stockfish) with potatoes.
Ingredients Salted, dried cod 1 kg potatoes (about 7) 2 garlic cloves, crushed 3 tbsp minced parsley 1 tbsp olive oil Directions Soak the fish in water for 24 hours, changing the water every few hours; this removes some of the salt and softens the dry fish Cut into pieces</description></item><item><title>Focaccia</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/foccacia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/foccacia/</guid><description>Description Almost no-knead focaccia, developed by David based on Grandma Giordano&amp;rsquo;s recipe (that wasn&amp;rsquo;t written down)
Ingredients 7 1/2 cups flour, 1/2 bread, 1/2 all purpose 1 tsp yeast 3 cups water 1 T salt Biga (old dough), about 1/2 cup. Skip if you don&amp;rsquo;t have Oil/salt for top Directions Preheat to 450 Mix flour, yeast, biga, water Add salt Knead until dough comes together, should be tacky Coat in oil and let rise overnight (8-24 hours) Stretch dough in jelly roll pan (or round) Let rise 1-2 hours Using hands, push dimples into dough, almost through to the pan Spray with water Coat in oil and sprinkle salt Put in oven (on tiles preferably) Add ice to a metal pan on floor of oven (for steam) Drop temp to 400 Bake 20-25 minutes</description></item><item><title>Gnocchi</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/potato-gnocchi/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 medium potatoes, cooked and riced 1 t. Salt, 1 t. Pepper 1 egg 1 c. Flour Directions Cook the potatoes in their skin. Cool and rice Add the rest of ingredients to the potatoes Form a long rope of about a foot Cut rope every one inch Run each over a grater to form indentation; or use a fork Cook in plenty of salted water They are done when they come to the top Serve with any sauce</description></item><item><title>Insalata Russa</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/insalata-russa/</guid><description>Description Grandma Giordano made this for special occasions, especially Easter.
Ingredients 1 lb frozen peas, cooked according to package 1 lb frozen cubed carrots, cooked according to package 2 large potatoes boiled and cubed Mayonnaise Directions Mix all together. Shape into oval and decorate with Olives, gherkins, capers, anchovies</description></item><item><title>La Sardenaira</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/sardenaira/</guid><description>Ingredients 4 cups flour 2 cups of warm water 1 pk of yeast 3 T. oil 1 T. salt 1 t. sugar Directions Mix the above together and let rise. Place dough in a pan and top with the following 1 can peeled tomatoes Oregano Garlic in their peel anchovies (optional) Olives - (taggiasche); substitute black cured Capers (optional) Olive oil Bake in a hot oven (475) until done (15 min) Notes Original recipe in Italian:</description></item><item><title>Pesto</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/pesto/</guid><description>Description Pesto can be made and frozen. If frozen do not add cheese or nuts; you can add those later, if you want.
Ingredients Basil Olive oil Garlic, multiple cloves Salt Parmesan cheese (optional) Pine nuts (optional) Directions Mix together in food processor Use right away or store in refrigerator (add oil to cover); or freeze When ready to use, warm up, add to pasta with a square of butter.</description></item><item><title>Ravioli</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/ravioli/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Stuffed Onions</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/stuffed-onions/</guid><description>Description Ingredients 3 medium size potatoes  4 tablespoon of extra-virgin olive oil  1 medium size onions, minced 1lb medium size white onions 2 eggs, lightly beaten 3 tablespoons freshly grated parmesan cheese 1 teaspoon of marjoram leaves, minced 1 tablespoon of fresh Italian (flat) parsley, minced fine sea salt to taste pepper to taste 1 cup fine unflavoured bread crumbs Directions Wash the potatoes, put them with their peel into a pot filled with cold water and boil for about 35 minutes or until tender.</description></item><item><title>Torta Verde</title><link>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidschober.github.io/recipes/torta-verde/</guid><description>Ingredients Dough:
3 cups flour 1 cup warm water 3/4 cup oil 1 T salt Inside:
2 big bunches Swiss chard chopped and steamed. Can substitute spinach 4 small-med zucchini, shredded 1/2 bag frozen or 2 cans artichokes chopped fine 3 eggs 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese (or Romano) Handful of rice Directions Dough:
Mix until smooth dough forms Flour surface to roll out dough; divide dough Roll out 2 sheets to fit pan top and bottom Bottom sheet is larger than first and should cover the pan with some dough hanging over the sides Top sheet is a little larger than pan Oil pan and add cornmeal then add bottom sheet and have some hang over Mix inside ingredients all together Add inside ingredients to pan, put top dough on and fold over bottom sheet edges with top sheet to form crust Make holes in the top to let air escape Top generously with olive oil Bake until golden brown 35/40 min.</description></item></channel></rss>